OK. Hello.
好的。 你好。
Banana.
香蕉。
Hello, guys.
大家好。
What's up?
怎么了？
Hey. Hey. Hi, everybody.
嘿。 嘿。 大家好你们好。
I told Leeds in the You didn't.
我告诉利兹你没有。
You didn't hear that, OK? No one heard that.
你没听到，好吗？ 没有人听说过。
Oh, my fucking God.
哦，我的他妈的上帝。
There are days.
有几天。
Where I'm just like, I'm so on top of it, right?
我在哪里就像，我在它上面，对吧？
I'm thinking so straight. I'm thinking so clearly.
我想的很直。 我想的很清楚。
And then I fuck up with laughter with, like, one thing, and it's
然后我笑得像一件事，通常总是麦克风。 哦，
But good morning, everybody.
但是大家早上好。
A good morning. Good morning.
早上好。 早上好。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Well, you're having a great day so far.
嗯，到目前为止，你今天过得很愉快。
Are you having a great morning so far?
到目前为止，你过得愉快吗？
You just woke up.
你刚刚醒来。
I am super, super excited.
我超级超级兴奋。
I really hope that our Internets doesn't grief us again today.
我真的希望我们的互联网今天不会再次让我们感到悲伤。
For people that don't know what happened last night
对于不知道昨晚发生了什么的人
because I didn't mention I forgot to post on Twitter by post on Discord, but
因为我没有提到我忘了在 Discord 上通过帖子在 Twitter 上发帖，但是
basically what happened
基本上昨天发生的事情是我们的互联网对自我感到畏缩。
So I couldn't really continue playing.
所以我真的不能继续玩了。
Poor I could.
可怜的我可以。
Turn off at the turn of text the speech real quick.
在文本的轮到关闭语音真的很快。
But, um, yeah, I had some issues with the Wi-Fi
但是，嗯，是的，我在使用 Wi-Fi 时遇到了一些问题
and it wasn't working properly.
它工作不正常。
Like a stream kept going on and off at times.
就像一条溪流时而时断时续。
So I had to end to end the live broadcast early.
所以我不得不提前结束直播。
So I'm really, really sorry about that. I don't know why.
所以我真的，真的很抱歉。 我不知道为什么。
Um, I've been having that issue, but,
嗯，我一直有这个问题，但是，你知道，我真的希望它不会发生在今天。
And I'm really,
我真的，再一次，我真的为人们感到难过
that, you know, couldn't
那，你知道，不能
that were there last night.
昨晚在那里。
But, you know, all those issues happens.
但是，你知道，所有这些问题都会发生。
Like, I feel bad about it, you know, like, I really do.
就像，我对此感到难过，你知道，就像，我真的如此。
I think that's like one of the biggest things that make me,
我认为这是让我最重要的事情之一，
you know, a little sad, if I'm going to be honest, is that,
你知道，有点难过，如果我要说实话，是不是，你知道，我有没有遇到那些不和谐的小问题
discord Internet problems because, like, you know, my service provider is sucky.
不和谐的互联网问题，因为，你知道，我的服务提供商很糟糕。
So I think I'm going to be changing my service provider because that's not OK.
所以我想我会改变我的服务提供商，因为那是不行的。
It's pretty bad, bro.
太糟糕了，兄弟。
It's pretty bad. Yeah.
这很糟糕。 是的。
And it's happened like, you know, every now and then.
你知道，它时不时地发生。
But som the fact that's happened this much is kind of
但是，发生了这么多的事实有点
kind of blair it's kind of cringe. So
有点布莱尔，有点畏缩。 所以
I try and avoid that from happening again.
我尽量避免这种情况再次发生。
Yeah.
是的。
You are there for all.
你在那里为所有人。
The donations and for the good service guys. It's OK.
捐赠和良好的服务人员。 没关系。
I'm fine.
我没事。
I like I rarely I.
我喜欢我很少我。
Get a rarely do I ever get sad or, like, genuinely upset over anything on stream
得到一个我很少会感到难过，或者，像，真正对直播中的任何事情感到不安
except for like, you know, internet problems because, like,
除了像，你知道的，互联网问题，因为，像，
that stuff it's, like, hard to control or it's like, hard to manage, right?
那些东西，就像，难以控制，或者就像，难以管理，对吧？
Like, you really can't saw you only can't do much
就像，你真的看不到你只能做很多事情
since you just got to sit there and, like, sit with it
因为你只需要坐在那里，就像，和它坐在一起
and you know, it sucks, bro.
你知道，这很糟糕，兄弟。
Everybody that has Internet problems know it sucks.
每个有互联网问题的人都知道这很糟糕。
Like, you know, you have plans of friends, like, online
喜欢，你知道，你有朋友的计划，喜欢，在线
or if you have stuff that you want to see will far you know other people.
或者，如果您有想看的东西，您就会认识其他人。
If you're a streamer like me, then,
如果你是像我这样的主播，那么，你知道，遇到这些问题，那就糟透了，兄弟。
That's kind of frustrating, but
这有点令人沮丧，但是
it's not the end of the world.
这不是世界末日。
I think it's OK today.
我觉得今天还可以。
I let's hope it's OK today.
我希望今天一切顺利。
If not, then. Oh, my goodness.
如果没有，那么。 哦，我的天啊。
I am going to I am going to stab, stab, stab a person
我要去我要去刺，刺，刺一个不是恶魔的人，这对我来说是很少见的。
You guys.
你们。
But aside from that, I am super duper
但除此之外，我非常兴奋能够完成今天的小噩梦。
Yeah, we're going to finish lol nightmares still.
是的，我们仍然要完成大声笑的噩梦。
And also after that, I think we're going to have time to finish home sweet home
在那之后，我想我们将有时间完成甜蜜的家
because
因为
we still haven't finished Home Sweet Home.
我们还没有完成 Home Sweet Home。
But I heard that there's like a couple of hours left in the game, so.
但我听说比赛还剩几个小时，所以。
I thought we could just do it all today.
我以为我们今天可以做到这一切。
Right.
对。
I'm also really liking Home Sweet Home.
我也很喜欢甜蜜的家。
You know why?
你知道为什么？
Because it's like
因为它就像
weaving in our nice.
编织在我们的美好。
What's it called?
这叫什么？
It's we've in good cultural beliefs and myths from, like, you know,
是我们有良好的文化信仰和神话，比如，你知道，
a different hour.
一个不同的小时。
I just enjoy.
我只是享受。
It when a game, like a good horror game can, like, implement good,
它当一个游戏，就像一个好的恐怖游戏一样，可以实现好的，
you know, like, culture into the game and be respectful of it
你知道，比如，将文化融入游戏并尊重它，你知道，我的意思是，这是一款泰国恐怖游戏，对吧？
So like, of course it'd be.
所以喜欢，当然会。
And the people that made it are I think they're Thai.
制作它的人是我认为他们是泰国人。
So is very accurate.
所以非常准确。
So like, you know, their beliefs and their mythologies and all that stuff.
所以就像，你知道的，他们的信仰和他们的神话等等。
So I think that's really cool.
所以我认为这真的很酷。
And I want to play more games like that because
我想玩更多这样的游戏，因为
I don't know.
我不知道。
Just it's cool.
只是很酷。
To learn about other people's like myths
了解别人喜欢的神话
and beliefs and like their urban legends and all of that.
和信仰，喜欢他们的都市传说等等。
You know, that's why I really enjoy, um, chilli's art games as well
你知道，这就是为什么我真的很喜欢，嗯，辣椒的艺术游戏
because it's very like heavy on, aside
因为它很重，除了喜欢一些更真实的东西或者它很重的东西，你知道，那些
Japanese culture and like different urban legends and stories you know.
日本文化，喜欢你知道的不同的都市传说和故事。
You can see side.
可以看到侧面。
Well, that's why I'm been.
嗯，这就是我一直存在的原因。
Having a lot of fun with it and I want to keep playing through more.
玩得很开心，我想继续玩更多。
And I don't know, I just can't I.
我不知道，我就是不能。
Can't hold myself back.
无法阻止自己。
I really just want to play more of it.
我真的只是想玩更多。
It's kind of like an excuse for me to just play more because I can sor
这对我来说有点像是一个借口，因为我可以多玩
I'm not patient and I see more of the I see the game because I've been enjoying
我没有耐心，我看到了更多我看到的比赛，因为我更享受自己。
I love working so much.
我非常喜欢工作。
There's so many people playing horror games they still like.
有很多人在玩他们仍然喜欢的恐怖游戏。
It's so cool. Right?
太酷了。 对？
I just really, really fucking love the fact that, you know,
我真的，真的他妈的喜欢这样一个事实，你知道，
I can
我可以
that so many more people are like, you know, getting their feet wet
这么多的人就像，你知道的，把他们的脚弄湿，如此恐怖，这不像是之前的经历
so it's getting to see more of my friends try it out
所以越来越多的朋友尝试了
and seeing other, you know, other streamers straight out.
并直接看到其他的，你知道的，其他飘带。
It makes me happy
这让我开心
it makes me Alvey Dog Boy.
它让我成为阿尔维狗男孩。
Roll the dice.
掷骰子。
They're fake.
他们是假的。
No, look, look, I can take him off anytime.
不，看，看，我可以随时把他带走。
Look, it's gone. Wow. Wow.
看，没了。 哇。 哇。
All Where's a dog, huh?
狗在哪里，对吧？
Rawalpindi. The dog. There's no. Dog.
拉瓦尔品第。 狗。 没有。 狗。
Oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
And then now it's back.
然后现在它又回来了。
Now it's back.
现在它回来了。
But it's.
但它的。
You can take it on and off. It doesn't mean I'm the dog. Though. Okay.
您可以打开和关闭它。 这并不意味着我是狗。 尽管。 好的。
It's just like, uh.
就像，呃。
It's just like an accessory you can put on.
它就像您可以戴上的配件。
It's like when you put on hair clips, right?
就像你戴上发夹一样，对吧？
No, I'm talking about.
不，我说的是。
So then you put on hair clips. Horror.
然后你戴上发夹。 恐怖。
Horror? Yeah.
恐怖？ 是的。
Where? Horror. Horror, horrors.
在哪里？ 恐怖。 恐怖，恐怖。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Okay, I'm going to turn off the music, though,
好的，不过我要关掉音乐，我认为现在是进入游戏的好时机。
Hi. Oh, today is my birthday.
你好。 哦，今天是我的生日。
Happy birthday.
生日快乐。
Smiles and happiness during these months.
在这几个月里，微笑和幸福。
Love you.
爱你。
1314.
1314.
I lead you, bro.
我带领你，兄弟。
Thank you for the dono and happy birthday.
谢谢你的捐赠和生日快乐。
Hope you have a great one at the birthday to you.
希望你在生日时有一个伟大的人。
Arsalan, thank you for the five younger subs.
Arsalan，谢谢你的五个年轻的潜艇。
Gly, thank you for that XL now.
Gly，谢谢你现在的 XL。
And that's Alfie. Thank you for the doll.
那就是阿尔菲。 谢谢你的娃娃。
No, I really appreciate all the support guys.
不，我真的很感谢所有支持的人。
It means a lot.
那意义重大。
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢你。 谢谢你。
I'm feeling a lot better today because, like, you know,
我今天感觉好多了，因为，你知道，
I have you guys have I have my guilds with me.
我有你们，我有我的公会。
So, you know, the whole the whole Internet, like
所以，你知道，整个互联网，就像
Baulking at self last night is sucks, but hey, it's OK.
昨晚对自己犹豫不决很糟糕，但是，嘿，没关系。
It's OK.
没关系。
We we're back now and hopefully everything will be fine.
我们现在回来了，希望一切都会好起来的。
Manifest good internets today, please.
请在今天展示良好的互联网。
If you guys believe in manifesting, then do that for me.
如果你们相信显化，那就为我做吧。
Manifest that.
表现出来。
We don't have any issues for the rest of the stream.
对于流的其余部分，我们没有任何问题。
Because, man,
因为，伙计，
Comcast has been has not been making me happy.
康卡斯特一直没有让我开心。
And that's probably the reason why, right?
这可能就是原因，对吧？
Because it's Comcast. Comcast, it sucks.
因为它是康卡斯特。 康卡斯特，太烂了。
OK, Alvey didn't hear that
好吧，阿尔维没有听到，因为我情绪低落，所以决定给我拔掉插头。
All right.
好的。
By the way, I do want to talk about something real quick
顺便说一句，我确实想快速谈谈一些事情
because like I did see people talking about this
因为就像我确实看到人们在谈论这个
I thought was really funny, but I just want you guys to remember,
我觉得很有趣，但我只是想让你们记住，就像，嘿，我是一个独立的人
streamer slash receiver, okay?
流光斜线接收器，好吗？
I'm by myself.
我一个人。
So that means like, I don't have
所以这意味着像，我没有
I'm not part of a company, right?
我不是公司的一员，对吧？
I don't have Gen mates.
我没有 Gen 队友。
Bloxham and Narcotics are not my gym mates.
Bloxham 和 Narcotics 不是我的健身房伙伴。
So, I mean, I.
所以，我的意思是，我。
Don't mind
别在意
I really don't mind being drawn with them all the time because like, it's cute.
我真的不介意一直被他们吸引，因为喜欢，它很可爱。
They're they're my friends are all of them are really friendly to me.
他们是他们是我的朋友，他们都对我非常友好。
And I love hanging out with them because they're cool. They're my friends.
我喜欢和他们一起出去玩，因为他们很酷。 他们是我的朋友。
That's, that's, that's totally fine.
那就是，那完全没问题。
But I just want to make sure people know, like, hey, I'm not, I'm not part of that.
但我只是想确保人们知道，比如，嘿，我不是，我不是其中的一部分。
I'm not in league. All right.
我不在联盟中。 好的。
And and that's.
就是这样。
Completely. Fine.
完全地。 美好的。
Like, I know some people thought I was for some odd reason,
就像，我知道有些人认为我是出于某种奇怪的原因，但我不是我只是我只是我自己。
I'm just not though I am.
我只是不是，虽然我是。
I have my own guild.
我有自己的公会。
We are our own.
我们是我们自己的。
You know,
你知道，
we're our own community.
我们是我们自己的社区。
Aside from that.
除此之外。
But like, they're still they're still my friends.
但就像，他们仍然是我的朋友。
They're very much still, like,
他们仍然非常安静，就像，非常棒和了不起的人，他们喜欢和他们一起出去玩，而且，
you know, play games with.
你知道，玩游戏。
But I just wanna make it clear that they I'm not part of that, and
但我只是想明确表示他们我不是其中的一部分，并且
it's I don't have to be a part of it, you know,
这是我不必成为其中的一部分，你知道，
like, I'm happy the way I am on my on my own.
就像，我很高兴我独自一人。
Like, that's why I'm sure.
就像，这就是我确定的原因。
All right. That's the only reason.
好的。 这是唯一的原因。
That's the only reason why I'm shopping right now
这就是我现在购物的唯一原因，因为我不是，你知道，我不是公司的一部分。
And I decide to be who I am by myself and on my own.
我决定做我自己和我自己的人。
Right?
对？
I just wanna make that a distinction
我只是想快速做出区分，这样人们就不会感到困惑。
Mm hmm. Shop for is shopper
嗯嗯。 购物就是购物者
I know you guys understand, but I just want to make that because I guess,
我知道你们明白，但我只是想这样做，因为我想，你知道，你周围有新人，他们可能不知道，
and there's a language barrier, so it'd be a bit confusing, I think.
并且存在语言障碍，所以我认为这会有点混乱。
And it's honestly like, not the worst association because, like,
老实说，这不是最糟糕的联想，因为，就像，
I do talk to them a lot, but, you know, it's like
我确实和他们聊了很多，但是，你知道，就像
they're they're my friends, so and I like talking to my friends
他们是我的朋友，所以我很喜欢和我的朋友聊天。
Oh, bowel.
哦，肠子。
Bowel me.
给我灌肠。
Thank you for the eats and gifts also.
也谢谢你的食物和礼物。
And I think if that's and gifts are still Sam, thank you for the donation and.
我想如果是这样，礼物仍然是 Sam，谢谢你的捐赠。
Friend.
朋友。
See I think there's a lot another said.
看到我想还有很多其他人说的。
Donations are friendly I can't read.
捐款很友好，我看不懂。
Your name.
你的名字。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I want to see company.
我想见公司。
See, I'm. Lovely.
看，我是。 迷人的。
Thank you for the gift sub. Yeah.
谢谢你的礼物子。 是的。
Thank you so much, bro.
太谢谢你了，兄弟。
Ah, that's for the sub.
啊，那是给潜艇的。
Your old house. Okay.
你的老房子。 好的。
Oh, that's Claire.
哦，那是克莱尔。
I think it's time we get into some horror games for tonight.
我想现在是我们今晚进入一些恐怖游戏的时候了。
I'm super excited, dude.
我超级兴奋，伙计。
I really, really was looking forward.
我真的，真的很期待。
So finishing up a nightmares one more time, and then we can head on.
所以再做一次噩梦，然后我们就可以继续前进了。
Saw actual on
看到实际
the main.
主要的。
Day last week, I only had the chance to be the main.
上周的一天，我只有机会成为主力。
Star of the. Show. They slept with you.
之星。 显示。 他们和你睡了。
I'm happy to have come since last year.
我很高兴从去年开始就来了。
And you really are my fave three months.
你真的是我最喜欢的三个月。
Thank you for being here.
非常感谢您的到来。
There is no problem there.
那里没有问题。
And hope you had a great birthday last week till.
并希望你上周生日快乐。
My God, there's only the amount of odds.
我的上帝，只有几率。
On nations.
论民族。
That come by, and we're like, hey, it's my birthday. Today.
那来了，我们就像，嘿，今天是我的生日。 今天。
It's my birthday today. It's my birthday today.
今天是我的生日。 今天是我的生日。
It's like, wow. Oh, my God.
就像，哇。 我的天啊。
But like I said before, I think it makes sense because, you know,
但就像我之前说的，我认为这是有道理的，因为，你知道，有很多人，一年只有
there's a lot of people and there's only 365 days in a year.
365 天。
So it's very likely today's your birthday.
所以今天很可能是你的生日。
Like, I feel like statistically it could be like
就像，我觉得从统计学上来说，现在可能是十个人的生日。
ten people's birthdays right now. Right? So yeah,
对？ 是的，
OK, let me switch on over to
好的，让我切换到
the video game
该视频游戏
oh, wait.
等一下。
I didn't click something.
我没有点击任何东西。
I didn't mean to
我不是故意的
oh, yeah, right.
哦，是的，对。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
My heart rate monitor hasn't been working at all for some reason.
由于某种原因，我的心率监测器根本无法工作。
Like, I have it connected and hooked up
就像，我把它连接起来了
um, maybe I need mm.
嗯，也许我需要mm。
I've never had this issue before is the thing
我以前从未遇到过这个问题
where, like, my heart rate monitor wasn't working,
在哪里，比如，我的心率监测器不工作，
you know,
你知道，
like, it only started happening
就像，它最近才因为某种原因才开始发生，我正试图找出原因。
That's why that's the problem.
这就是问题所在。
Not sure mm.
不确定mm。
Yep. I have a heart.
是的。 我有一颗心。
And while there, I installed the conveyor widgets
在那里，我安装了传送带小部件
stall. Yup,
摊位。 是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。
But I really want to have my heart rate monitor on the screen.
但我真的很想在屏幕上显示我的心率监测器。
I don't know why. It's like.
我不知道为什么。 它像是。
Oh, says it's off line.
哦，说是离线。
Oh, now it's all mine.
哦，现在都是我的了。
Huh huh. What, what?
呵呵。 什么什么？
What bruh?
什么兄弟？
My maximum heart rate is 179,
我的最高心率是 179，我的最低心率是 50 白色。
How's it know that?
它怎么知道的？
Oh, that's crazy.
哦，那太疯狂了。
OK, use the euro and just launch it.
好的，使用欧元并启动它。
Launch OK.
启动确定。
It should be there now.
它现在应该在那里。
What's not there?
什么不存在？
Why is it not there?
为什么不存在？
Yeah, once I, you know, I was.
是的，曾经我，你知道，我是。
My heart was the highest it's ever gone. Hm.
我的心是有史以来最高的。 嗯。
I I'm confused.
我很困惑。
Why is it not showing up?
为什么不显示？
Do you guys see anything on your screen?
你们在屏幕上看到什么了吗？
Hmm? And use window capture
唔？ 并使用窗口捕获
uh, hold on a second.
呃，等一下。
I could just use window capture.
我可以只使用窗口捕获。
Right?
对？
That that's definitely an option.
那绝对是一种选择。
Mm. I'm not sure.
毫米。 我不确定。
All guys, it's not my birthday.
各位，今天不是我的生日。
I think. I think you guys.
我认为。 我想你们。
I think you guys are confuse because like, no, I didn't say it's my birthday.
我认为你们很困惑，因为就像，不，我没有说这是我的生日。
It's, um.
是，嗯。
I'm just
我只是说看到很多人说，嘿，今天是我的生日。
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
Right?
对？
I wasn't trying to say it was my birthday.
我不是想说这是我的生日。
It's not my birthday.
这不是我的生日。
Sally.
莎莉。
Oh, there it is.
哦，是的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
走吧，走吧，走吧。
It's back, baby.
它回来了，宝贝。
Whoa! Oh, my God.
哇！ 我的天啊。
We got to work again.
我们又得工作了。
Judah.
犹大。
Holy shit.
天啊。
That made me so fucking happy.
这让我他妈的太高兴了。
What the hell?
我勒个去？
It works.
有用。
Oh, I got to works.
哦，我要上班了。
OK, nice.
好的，不错。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Now we don't talk.
现在我们不说话了。
Now we don't have to worry about that anymore.
现在我们不必再担心这个了。
Okay, cool.
好的，酷。
Yeah, cool.
是的，酷。
Also, hold on really quick.
另外，坚持得很快。
Let me just
让我只是
do one more thing
再做一件事
oh, you are.
哦，你是。
You're very on time. You're very on time.
你很准时。 你很准时。
Who is it?
是谁？
I need to like I need to figure.
我需要喜欢我需要弄清楚。
Out which one of.
出哪一个。
You motherfuckers is doing that.
你们这些混蛋正在这样做。
Who is it, huh?
是谁，嗯？
It's been so many times.
已经这么多次了。
That they are that they activate that sound or who.
他们就是他们激活那个声音或谁。
Is. It's call them out right now.
是。 现在是叫他们出来。
Who's doing that, huh?
是谁在做的，嗯？
Who's doing that?
谁在这样做？
I still don't know who it is.
我还是不知道是谁。
Like after all this time, there's always one person.
就像过了这么久，总有一个人。
There's always that one person who does it.
总有那么一个人在做。
When I try to hide myself, they're so fast.
当我试图隐藏自己时，他们是如此之快。
Today. Deal.
今天。 交易。
Was it because last night I said, your slow ha Dianne your Dianne
是不是因为昨晚我说，你的慢哈黛安你的黛安你的神经都消失了。
Your fucking nerves will baby. Oh, fucking baby.
你他妈的神经会宝贝。 哦，他妈的宝贝。
Come couldn't embarrass me last night because you were too slow.
昨晚来了不能让我难堪，因为你太慢了。
All stupid.
都傻了。
Who was it?
他是谁？
Who the fuck was it? It
到底是谁？ 它也，我说谢谢你。
Send gifts obviously would appreciate it, man.
送礼物显然会很感激，伙计。
Awesome.
惊人的。
Some kind of blue
某种蓝色
I know it's a little.
我知道这是一点点。
Blue invites like to match with the background.
蓝色邀请喜欢与背景相匹配。
I don't know how I don't know how much you guys like that but.
我不知道我怎么不知道你们有多喜欢那样但是。
All is shit.
一切都是狗屎。
Annie thank you.
安妮谢谢你。
For the 50 gift subs.
对于 50 礼品潜艇。
Holy fuck.
他妈的。
Thank you so much for 50 gifts.
非常感谢你送的 50 份礼物。
Obviously I'll be having a great day.
显然，我将度过美好的一天。
Oh, one.
哦，一个。
We give you a
我们给你一个
uh. Uh.
呃。 呃。
That's for everyone.
那是给每个人的。
But, like, you know,
但是，就像，你知道的，作为一个小礼物。
Yeah, I'm a little blue right now, but I.
是的，我现在有点蓝，但我。
Hope that's OK. Do you guys do you guys prefer.
希望没关系。 你们喜欢吗。
On on I want to know your preferences.
我想知道你的喜好。
Do you guys like it when I'm a yeah.
当我是的时候，你们喜欢吗？
Do you guys like it when I'm blending with the background?
当我与背景融合时，你们喜欢它吗？
A little bit like natural, the environments a little bit more?
有点像自然，环境多一点？
Or do you do you prefer it if it's
或者你更喜欢它，如果它是
you prefer if it's off like this,
你更喜欢这样关闭，
so when you blend in
所以当你融入或者你想要它关闭时
OK, you can get a vote on it.
好的，你可以投票。
Sure, sure, sure.
确定，确定，确定。
I have myself I'll blend in or not blend in
我有自己 我会融入或不融入
because either way, I really don't mind.
因为不管怎样，我真的不介意。
It's based on like what you guys want.
它是基于你们想要的。
I thought I'd try out because I don't I rarely.
我以为我会尝试，因为我很少这样做。
Gets the, you know, blend myself in.
得到，你知道的，融入其中。
By the way, if you guys got any gift subsidy or from your series till be shirts
顺便说一句，如果你们得到任何礼物补贴或从你的系列直到成为衬衫
give the people that's gifted subs a big thank you.
非常感谢那些有天赋的人。
All right.
好的。
If you got one yourself
如果你自己有一个
I think a lot of people want the the blend.
我想很多人都想要混合。
OK, you know what?
好的，你知道吗？
I'll do that
我去做
yeah.
是的。
Seems like a lot of people do. All right. Give me a second.
好像很多人都这样。 好的。 你稍等一会儿。
Give me
再给我一秒钟。
OK? Should be good now.
好的？ 现在应该好了。
Last time we left off,
上次我们离开的时候，我们就像要进城了。
I wonder.
我想知道。
Hold on. Give me a second.
坚持，稍等。 你稍等一会儿。
Give me a one.
给我一个。
One second.
一秒。
This is weird.
这很奇怪。
Yes. Because, like, I want to make sure, like,
是的。 因为，就像，我想确保，就像，一切正常，好吗？
So blue.
这么蓝。
I feel so blue.
我觉得好蓝
Attack OK.
攻击OK。
I think that's all it's how it's supposed to be
我认为这就是它应该是的一切
is the environment's really blue chill?
环境真的是蓝色的寒意吗？
So I think that's why there's a lot of blue light.
所以我认为这就是为什么有很多蓝光的原因。
Or back of mono and sex.
或单声道和性别的背面。
Hey there, buddy.
嘿，伙计。
Go hold your hand now.
现在去牵你的手。
Yeah.
是的。
This dude died
这哥们死了
He ran into the TV for some reason. Why
不知为何，他冲进了电视机。 为什么
I think I.
我想我。
Right. I think these guys, like, are, like,
对。 我认为这些人，就像，是，像，
hypnotised or something.
催眠什么的。
By it.
通过它。
Have I found in the hats in the game?
我在游戏中的帽子里找到了吗？
Yeah, I have found hats in the game already.
是的，我已经在游戏中找到了帽子。
A few hats
几顶帽子
I think the real horror here
我认为这里真正的恐怖将是避免。
All this, huh?
这一切，嗯？
Oh. Oh, hey there.
哦。 哦，嘿那里。
I'm happy to meet with you live today.
我很高兴今天能和你见面。
Oh, I turn off Texas beach, dude.
哦，我关掉了德克萨斯海滩，伙计。
I keep forgetting to do that. Are
我一直忘记这样做。 是
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I'll read out the donations and stuff at the end of stream
我会在直播结束时读出捐款和东西
he doesn't see me right
他看错了我
so I think I'm fine.
所以我觉得我很好。
Yeah, these guys don't see me.
是的，这些家伙看不到我。
They're just focussed on the TV.
他们只是专注于电视。
I don't, do I?
我没有，是吗？
But if I throw it out her,
但如果我把它扔给她，
I throw it out.
我把它扔掉。
You on
你继续
no. She doesn't give a shit.
不。 她一点都不在乎。
Really.
真的。
Low top.
低帮。
OK. OK, yeah, she gives a shit also.
好的。 好的，是的，她也很讨厌。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I think, I think it might be broken.
我想，我想它可能会坏掉。
Guys are for some reason the arm. It's not doing
伙计们出于某种原因是手臂。 它没有做
exactly the way that I wanted to so I might have to actually turn it off
正是我想要的方式，所以我今天可能不得不把它关掉，因为它一直保持蓝色，而且不应该这样。
And it's like a very awkward, it's very awkward how it's doing it.
它就像一个非常尴尬的，它是如何做的非常尴尬。
So I don't like that.
所以我不喜欢那样。
We're just gonna turn off for now. Yeah.
我们只是暂时关闭。 是的。
And then maybe we'll fix it.
然后也许我们会修复它。
So next time
所以下次
that's ok.
那没问题。
Yeah. Thank you.
是的。 谢谢你。
Thanks for understanding.
感谢您的理解。
Because, like, when it goes to black,
因为，就像，当它变成黑色时，它也应该与黑色融为一体，但它不会那样做。
it should also blend in with the black, but it doesn't do that. So
所以
it's weird.
真奇怪。
But. Yeah, but
但。 好但是
that doesn't look safe.
那看起来不安全。
Isn't that, like, you know what?
不就是这样，你知道吗？
If it falls into the.
如果落入。
Bathtub and you get electrocuted, is that like, how people say,
浴缸，你会触电，就像人们所说的那样，不要在浴缸附近使用吹风机之类的东西
oh, that's fine.
哦，那很好。
We're just gonna ignore him.
我们只会无视他。
That's not our problem.
那不是我们的问题。
Can I push the TV?
我可以推电视吗？
You only push the TV.
你只推电视。
And so that's cruel.
所以这是残酷的。
That's cruel, bro.
太残忍了，兄弟。
On boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
在繁荣，繁荣，繁荣，繁荣，繁荣。
It sounds like the Barney song.
这听起来像巴尼的歌。
I love you.
我爱你。
You love me.
你爱我。
You all that.
你这一切。
I hated the Barney song.
我讨厌巴尼的歌。
Life is super creepy, man.
生活真是令人毛骨悚然，伙计。
Wait, how do I. Huh?
等等，我该怎么做。嗯？
Oops.
哎呀。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Barney was cute.
巴尼很可爱。
Barney's creepy, Vanya scary.
巴尼令人毛骨悚然，万尼亚吓人。
And there are like, that purple fucker the.
还有像，那个紫色的混蛋。
Sorry, guys.
对不起大家。
I just he he scared me a lot when I was a kid.
我只是他，当我还是个孩子的时候，他让我很害怕。
Yeah.
是的。
Let's see what's over here.
让我们看看这里有什么。
Check inside
检查里面
Barney got arrested.
巴尼被捕。
I think. You know what?
我认为。 你知道吗？
It adds up.
它加起来。
It adds up to me.
它加起来我。
Makes sense.
说得通。
It's it's creepy.
这是令人毛骨悚然的。
Oh, that's how we got up here.
哦，我们就是这样上来的。
OK, nice
不错，不错
lie. I'm sorry.
说谎。 对不起。
It's a lot to everybody else.
对其他人来说很多。
I just. I couldn't. I couldn't really.
我只是。 我不能。 我真的不能。
I he.
我他。
Sports. He's so spooky, man.
运动的。 他太吓人了，伙计。
I don't like his beautiful eyes and just
我不喜欢他美丽的眼睛，只是
his smile.
他的笑容。
His creepy little smile.
他那令人毛骨悚然的小微笑。
We found a key
我们找到了一把钥匙
as long as I like Thomas the Tank Engine.
只要我喜欢坦克引擎托马斯。
I you know, I kind.
我知道，我很善良。
Of like Thomas the Tank Engine.
就像坦克引擎托马斯一样。
Yeah, he's OK.
是的，他没事。
He didn't really carry me all that much.
他并没有真正带我那么多。
Teletubbies creeps me out, though.
不过天线宝宝让我毛骨悚然。
I don't like Teletubbies.
我不喜欢天线宝宝。
A funky so you can come inside now.
一个时髦的，所以你现在可以进来了。
Hey, a friend. Friend
嘿，一个朋友。 朋友
are you going to help me?
你要帮我吗？
Come on. Come on.
来吧。 来吧。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Wait, what was I supposed to do?
等等，我该怎么办？
Oh, ok. OK.
哦好的。 好的。
Never mind.
没关系。
I think I get it.
我想我明白了。
No, I think I get it.
不，我想我明白了。
Teletubbies are a nightmare in itself.
天线宝宝本身就是一场噩梦。
Why not? It's not really the.
为什么不？ 它不是真的。
Teletubbies that scared. Me.
天线宝宝好害怕。 我。
It was the sun, the baby sun.
那是太阳，婴儿太阳。
And, like, the way that they talked
而且，就像，他们说话的方式
the way that they talked, it's like
他们说话的方式，就像
it reminds me of the way mist.
它让我想起了雾的方式。
That's OK.
那没问题。
Sometimes
有时
does that mean.
这是否意味着。
I don't know. I don't think that's mean.
我不知道。 我不认为那是卑鄙的。
You know, that voice, that silly little voice.
你知道，那个声音，那个愚蠢的小声音。
He does oral
他做口头
yeah. The baby.
是的。 宝宝。
The sun was just weird to me. I didn't like it.
太阳对我来说很奇怪。 我不喜欢它。
I didn't like looking at it.
我不喜欢看它。
Wow. Yeah, that's cool.
哇。 是的，这很酷。
That's really cool.
这真的很酷。
I fully expect to see a sea art of mystery.
我完全期待看到神秘的海洋艺术。
The Teletubbies.
天线宝宝。
Now, I think they'll make him really, really mould.
现在，我想他们会让他真的，真的模子。
You know, you guys
你们知道吗
seeing him as what's it?
看他是什么东西？
Because on
因为在
the the whole high school musical
整个高中音乐剧
character.
特点。
Who's this guy.
他是谁。
Oh, hey there, my friend.
哦，嘿，我的朋友。
Now I think.
现在我想。
Oh, my God, there's rats inside.
哦，天哪，里面有老鼠。
Are these rats
这些老鼠是
like all these rats?
像所有这些老鼠一样？
Look at the boys.
看看男生。
They're all dead though.
不过他们都死了。
Them after the after the boys
他们在男孩们之后
squeak, squeak, squeak.
吱，吱，吱。
Yeah.
是的。
And I think he actually was like moulding over
而且我认为他实际上就像在塑造人们保留里面的东西的事实
making that association, and it makes me laugh.
建立这种关联，这让我发笑。
It's funny.
这很有趣。
No, I can't open the door one more.
不，我不能再打开门了。
I suppose all.
我想都是。
I can open the door
我可以开门
the rats are kind of cute, though.
不过，老鼠有点可爱。
You guys are kind of cute.
你们有点可爱
I like to be.
我喜欢当。
Let's try and be a little sweet.
让我们试着甜一点。
Once in a while. We.
偶尔。 我们。
How do we get that over? Oh, no, no, no.
我们如何解决这个问题？ 哦，不，不，不。
I think.
我认为。
Hey, you lift me up
嘿，你举起我举起我，助我一臂之力，助我一臂之力，兄弟。
Boost, boost, boost. And get a boost.
提升，提升，提升。 并获得提升。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Yeah.
是的。
And then I think she's supposed to grab on to that and roll over also.
然后我认为她应该抓住那个并翻身。
Michael And thank you for that. Sincere ones.
迈克尔 谢谢你。 真诚的。
There's a. Lot of. Yourselves for us.
有个。 许多。 为我们自己。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
And share all the support and love
并分享所有的支持和爱
give you a smooch
给你一个吻，如果可以的话，
if that is acceptable.
如果这是可以接受的。
I still like I'm still like wondering
我仍然喜欢我仍然想知道为什么我们还要一起踏上这段小旅程。
Is this like, a
这像，一个
we're trying to get out
我们正试图离开这里或喜欢什么，目的是什么？
I know we've been walking around and running around to try and like you know,
我知道我们一直在四处走动和跑来跑去，就像你知道的那样，
get away from those weirdos.
远离那些怪人。
But at the same time, why are we doing this?
但与此同时，我们为什么要这样做？
Why we are why are we here?
我们为什么在这里？
You're shot.
你被枪杀了。
The game was multiplayer.
游戏是多人游戏。
Imagine if the game was multiplayer.
想象一下，如果游戏是多人游戏。
Oh my God, I'd be so. Cool, right?
哦，我的上帝，我会这样。 很酷，对吧？
I thought the.
我以为。
Game was going to be multiplayer on the first game out but no,
游戏将在第一场比赛中进行多人游戏，但没有，
it wasn't
不是
I would have loved to play a friend
我很想扮演一个朋友
I'm just a little guy.
我只是一个小家伙。
We're all just little guys.
我们都只是小家伙。
Those little world.
那些小世界。
Little guy can conquer the world on his birthday.
小家伙可以在生日那天征服世界。
Would you
你会
want functional games?
想要功能性游戏？
Birthday? Would you? It's happening
生日？ 你会？ 它正在发生
hello.
你好。
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, that's bad.
哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，那太糟糕了。
Oh, that's bad.
哦，那很糟糕。
Oh, we got to run.
哦，我们得跑了。
Over which way?
过哪条路？
Oh, no.
不好了。
I thought we died.
我以为我们死了。
Oh, six.
哦，六个。
Whoa!
哇！
Oh, no sex.
哦，没有性。
Wait, hello?
等等，喂？
Sex. Sex.
性别。 性别。
How are you?
你好吗？
Still alive.
还活着。
And you get crushed under all of that.
你会被这一切压垮。
I am glad she's OK.
我很高兴她没事。
But it looked like she got destroyed underneath that stuff down.
但看起来她在那些东西下面被摧毁了。
Lucky
幸运的
Earth.
地球。
I hold your I hold your hand.
我握着你我握着你的手。
So, Beth, thank you for the laugh.
所以，贝丝，谢谢你的笑声。
I guess up still.
估计还在
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
Dude.
老兄。
If if she actually, like, broke her legs there during that part,
如果她真的，就像在那段时间里摔断了腿，
I would have been so sad, like, genuinely upset.
我会很伤心，就像，真的很沮丧。
And we can't we have to, like, move on without her.
我们不能像没有她一样继续前进。
That would make me really fucking
那会让我真的他妈的什么？ 为什么跳得那么高？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
What?
什么？
Why me?
为什么是我？
Why am I able to jump so high here?
为什么我能在这里跳这么高？
This doesn't look right it doesn't feel
这看起来不对，感觉不对。 嗯？
That's weird.
这很奇怪。
OK, I just didn't expect
好吧，我只是没想到
I hope she never dies.
我希望她永远不会死。
No, not again.
不，不再。
You just walk away from it.
你只是远离它。
It's time to go back in.
是时候回去了。
So I go back into the TV world
所以我回到电视世界
and see what the fuck is up
看看到底怎么回事
oh, this is weird.
哦，这很奇怪。
Why are
为什么是
every time we do that, I don't.
每次我们这样做，我不这样做。
I know we're trying to, like, tune it
我知道我们正在尝试将其调整到频率，但是
I only wish you'd open that door, bro.
我只希望你打开那扇门，兄弟。
It seems like a bad idea.
这似乎是个坏主意。
I think we should open that door.
我认为我们应该打开那扇门。
Or six.
或六个。
He's outside.
他在外面。
Not in the not in the TV.
不在电视里。
Or hello.
或者你好。
Who's inside
谁在里面
oh, hey, it's Slenderman.
哦，嘿，是Slenderman。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
Is he coming?
他来了吗？
Always, always.
总是，总是。
Hey, we should run.
嘿，我们应该跑。
I think. I think we should run, dude.
我认为。 我认为我们应该逃跑，伙计。
Yeah, yeah. This is not very funny anymore.
是啊是啊。 这已经不是很有趣了。
It's not funny anymore.
这已经不好笑了。
Put, don't run.
放，不要跑。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
Sex. Sex.
性别。 性别。
Are we alone?
我们是一个人吗？
She's gone.
她走了。
She's.
她的。
Oh, I mean.
哦，我是说。
We've just got to go back inside
我们只需要回到里面把她弄好
yeah.
是的。
Where
在哪里
the fuck.
他妈的。
Dude?
老兄？
What's all of the the creepy look and I and all the all the guts and
什么是令人毛骨悚然的样子，我和所有所有的胆量和
and squishy bits.
和软软的位。
That's sad, though.
不过，这很可悲。
Was that was like our buddy since the beginning.
那是不是就像我们从一开始的伙伴一样。
Now she's gone
现在她走了
now he's all by himself again.
现在他又是一个人了。
He's all alone.
他一个人。
Yeah. I go. I'll go save her friend.
是的。 我去。 我会去救她的朋友。
From the weird TV man with the fedora.
来自戴着软呢帽的奇怪电视人。
He has a fucking fedora
他有一个他妈的软呢帽
I like that a lot.
我非常喜欢那个。
The it's cool way of transporting. And.
这是一种很酷的运输方式。 和。
Why you want
你为什么要
oh, ok.
哦好的。
OK. Right. I think yeah.
好的。 对。 我想是的。
That's a bring the TV to the other side
那是将电视带到另一边并使用门户
that's going to be like
这会有点像
portal puzzle.
门户之谜。
I don't know what to call it.
我不知道该怎么称呼它。
Now. There's basically portal puzzles.
现在。 基本上有门户谜题。
Yeah.
是的。
I like it.
我喜欢。
I like it though.
不过我喜欢。
It's, I think a bit more
是的，我想多了
now. What I don't like though,
现在。 不过我不喜欢的，
are those weird motherfuckers.
是那些奇怪的混蛋。
Those guys of the warped faces are looking at the TVs.
那些歪着脸的家伙正在看电视。
What are those monsters called?
那些怪物叫什么？
Do they even have a name?
他们甚至有名字吗？
Are they just the adults are going crazy because all of them are like looking at
他们只是成年人都快疯了，因为他们都喜欢看电视被它吸收。
Oh, I died. Oh.
哦，我死了。 哦。
What high die
什么高死
I mean, how do you mean aliens?
我的意思是，你是什么意思外星人？
I jumped the fuck off.
我他妈的跳了。
What am I supposed to go, though?
不过，我该怎么走？
Up here?
上面这儿？
Oh, dude, I'm my my my eyes are.
哦，伙计，我是我的眼睛。
Just I'm just blind sorry.
只是我瞎了抱歉。
I don't have a good depth perception
我没有很好的深度感知
I'm cringe, Your Honour.
我畏缩了，法官大人。
No cap
没有上限
you know
你知道它发出的电视噪音就像听起来一样。
It sounds like.
这听起来像。
How how do you die from that brawl, mano?
你怎么会死于那场争吵，马诺？
Sorry, Mano. I'm sorry.
对不起，马诺。 对不起。
It kind of reminds.
它有点提醒。
You of
你的
oh, I live.
哦，我活着。
Holy shit.
天啊。
I lived there.
我住在那里。
Yeah. Reminds me of them.
是的。 让我想起了他们。
What's it called?
这叫什么？
Arcade
拱廊
soft.
柔软的。
I would hear from an arcade
我会从游戏的街机听到。
Oh, hmm.
哦，嗯。
They just gives that particular vibe, I guess.
我猜他们只是给人一种特别的感觉。
Yeah, like those.
是的，像那些。
There's certain, like, arcade games and, like,
有某些，比如，街机游戏，比如，
crying games that make like, a lot of, like, music.
制作类似，很多，喜欢，音乐的哭泣游戏。
So silly music noises like that.
如此愚蠢的音乐噪音。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I think that's a move. This
我认为这是一个举措。 这
if I move,
如果我动了，那就是我跳过去的平台。
Wow. This e
哇。 这个电子
arcade music real a lot.
街机音乐真的很多。
Sometimes it's really.
有时确实如此。
Arcade music is nice, though. Gives me some.
不过街机音乐很好听。 给我一些。
It gives me a nostalgia boner
它让我怀旧
you ever hear of that term nostalgia boner?
你听说过怀旧这个词吗？
Me neither.
我也不。
It makes zero sense.
它是零意义的。
I still use it anyways.
反正我还在用。
You're probably drunk right now.
你现在可能喝醉了。
I'm not drunk.
我没醉。
Sir. It is
先生。 这是
9:43 a.m.. In the morning.
上午 9 点 43 分。早上。
Why would I be drunk?
为什么我会喝醉？
I have not consumed any alcohol.
我没有喝过任何酒。
Well, e
嗯，e
as you
如你所知，我在这里啊。
OK. That's creepy.
好的。 那是令人毛骨悚然的。
But what the fuck am I supposed to do?
但我他妈的该怎么办？
Yeah, how am I supposed to
是啊，我该怎么做
am I?
我是吗？
Am I supposed to hide from her?
我应该躲着她吗？
Yeah, I think I'm supposed to do something off the TV.
是的，我想我应该在电视之外做点什么。
Well, I'm not sure what it is.
好吧，我不确定它是什么。
Yeah, I think I had to, like, get through the TV by to get her away from it.
是的，我想我必须，比如，通过电视让她远离它。
Well, how
嗯，怎么
you hide first?
你先躲起来？
Yeah. Where do I hide?
是的。 我躲在哪里？
Where should I hide?
我应该躲在哪里？
She ate me.
她吃了我。
What was I supposed to hide there? Hmm?
我应该在那里隐藏什么？ 唔？
Damn it!
该死的！
Damn it, Jim. It's
该死的，吉姆。 它是
what's that song, though?
那首歌是什么歌呢？
I don't know.
我不知道。
To keep the door open to the door open.
让门一直开着，门就开着。
Fuck, no, no.
他妈的，不，不。
The door is closing
门正在关闭
yeah.
是的。
Where am I supposed to hide from her?
我应该在哪里躲着她？
Like back here.
就像回到这里。
Oh, guys,
哦，伙计们，
I don't know where to go, or I must watch the fridge.
我不知道该去哪里，否则我必须看好冰箱。
Maybe throw something.
也许扔东西。
There's a TV.
有一台电视机。
Oh, you're right. There's a TV outside.
哦，你是对的。 外面有电视。
It's right there.
它就在那里。
Wait, so maybe she'll go to that one
等等，也许她会去那个
that you happen to have?
你碰巧有？
That was stupid. OK.
那是愚蠢的。 好的。
So now I can go through this, right?
所以现在我可以通过这个了，对吧？
And where is it?
它在哪里？
Take me now.
现在带我去。
OK, turn this off.
好的，关掉这个。
Let me turn the TV off. OK,
让我关掉电视。 好的，
you want the kitchen to call her stupid?
你想让厨房骂她傻？
Of course.
当然。
Yeah,
是的，
I don't know why.
我不知道为什么。
They turn into those, like, warped face creatures, though.
不过，它们变成了那些像扭曲的面孔一样的生物。
If they're, like, just if they were regular people
如果他们是，就像，就像他们是普通人一样
and then they just suck you in.
然后他们就把你吸进去了。
Like this guy right here. It's you.
就像这里的这个人。 是你。
Look at him.
看着他。
Hold on. Wait.
坚持，稍等。 等待。
Like an.
像一个。
Evolved.
进化。
That's fucked up.
那是完蛋了。
That's so fucked up, bro. All
太坑爹了兄弟 全部
by me, I guess.
由我，我猜。
Better. Better him than me.
更好的。 他比我好。
I don't want to die.
我不要死。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
Off mono, mono
关闭单声道，单声道
yeah.
是的。
Yeah.
我猜他们对它如此着迷，以至于他们甚至都不注意自己的周围环境。
They just walk off anything.
他们只是走开任何东西。
They only fixate on the TV.
他们只盯着电视。
I Jarvis nor
我贾维斯也不
I press the jump button.
我按下跳跃键。
I swear.
我发誓。
I swear I did
我发誓我做到了
you hear that?
你听到了吗？
I'm pressing jump right now.
我现在按跳跃。
I press the jump on.
我按下跳跃键。
I do that to me
我对我这样做
as I do.
像我这样做。
That's me.
那是我。
You guys
你们
Bruce.
布鲁斯。
No, I thought those were bodies hanging out there.
不，我以为那些是挂在那里的尸体。
And now these are people huh?
现在这些是人吧？
Why are they falling off the building?
为什么他们会从大楼上掉下来？
Why are they all falling
为什么他们都从大楼上掉下来
the aliens? No,
外星人？ 不，
I don't think so,
我不这么认为，
bro. Bro, what
兄弟。 兄弟，什么
am I supposed to not do that
我不应该那样做吗
hold on.
坚持，稍等。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Give me a second.
你稍等一会儿。
Let me try and save myself
让我试着救自己一个，好吗？ 好的。
Maybe I should go outside and pull the TV.
也许我应该到外面去拉电视。
So that I don't. Die
所以我没有。 死
or maybe I should push the tv down.
或者我应该把电视推下去。
Yeah, I like that.
是的，我喜欢这样。
That makes a lot more sense.
这更有意义。
I'm not a knowledge on laker.
我对湖人不是很了解。
I can't.
我不能。
I can't park
我不能停车
off. Of our
离开。 我们的建筑物，操作和建筑物的侧面。
OK, he can
好的，他可以
we that you.
我们就是你。
All electrocute
所有的水电死我们。
Are there's something on the other side of that door.
那扇门的另一边有什么东西吗？
I think we're going to have to run from it.
我认为我们将不得不逃避它。
Oh. Ha.
哦。 哈。
Oh, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不。
Don't hurt me.
不要伤害我。
Come dumb-ass hat.
来个笨蛋帽子。
I forgot four.
我忘记了四个。
Oh, my God. I forgot to turn off the
我的天啊。 我忘了关掉
I forgot to.
我忘了。
Turn it off before I walked back in
在我走进去之前把它关掉
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
OK, it's it's fine. It's fine.
好的，没关系。 没事。
We know what to do now.
我们知道现在该做什么。
Everything calm.
一切平静。
I just. I was.
我只是。 我曾是。
Look, I
看，我
I just forgot what
我只是忘记了发生了什么。
Now it's turn it back off, ok?
现在是把它关掉，好吗？
He was a lot faster this time.
这次他的速度快了很多。
I mean, that was just more slow.
我的意思是，这只是更慢。
Now it's really fucking quiet.
现在真的很安静。
It'll be.
这将是。
All. Nasty on the creepy music, man.
全部。 讨厌令人毛骨悚然的音乐，伙计。
It's really creepy music.
这真是令人毛骨悚然的音乐。
Can weird
可以很奇怪
a TV.
一台电视。
There's a TV inside the elevator.
电梯里有电视。
I think.
我认为。
Are we supposed to get back inside now?
我们现在应该回到里面吗？
Oh, hold on, hold on.
哦，等一下，等一下。
I think we use this as.
我想我们用这个作为。
Like, our little old stuff stool
就像，我们的小旧东西凳子
it's like, jump up and open up the switch.
就像，跳起来打开开关。
Yeah. What's that music did?
是的。 那音乐是做什么的？
Does anybody know where that music's from?
有谁知道这音乐出自哪里？
It sounds familiar.
听起来很熟悉。
Unless it's, like, you know, just some random gibberish
除非是，就像，你知道的，只是一些随机的胡言乱语
and if it is an OK
如果没问题
womp, womp, whatever,
womp，womp，无论如何，
way, I think I understand what I got to do.
方式，我想我明白我必须做什么。
I think.
我认为。
It's you I huh.
是你我哈。
Do I understand. What I see?
我明白吗。 我所看到的？
You give me a second. Hmm?
你给我一秒钟。 唔？
Ha. OK, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
哈。 好的，等一下，等一下，等一下，等一下。
How do I.
我如何。
There's, like, those. Windows at the top.
有，就像，那些。 窗户在顶部。
I know how to get on the top of the elevator, but how.
我知道怎么上电梯，但是怎么上。
Do I do that?
我这样做吗？
Jump through the whole
跳过整个
yeah.
是的。
I don't know how to jump through the hole.
我不知道如何跳过这个洞。
How long oh.
多久哦。
All right, all right, all right. All right, all right.
好的，好的，好的。 好吧，好吧。
Paul The pa pa pa pa pa pa pa pa pa pa
保罗 爸 爸 爸 爸 爸
wait. Pop.
等待。 流行音乐。
Oh, hold on, hold on.
哦，等一下，等一下。
No, no, no, no, no, no. I get it.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不。 我得到它。
Hold on, hold on, hold on. Wait, wait.
坚持，坚持，坚持。 等等。
I understand. Now give me some
我明白。 现在给我一些
Everything's.
一切都是。
Everything's connecting. Everything's connecting. Now.
一切都在连接。 一切都在连接。 现在。
I got it.
我得到了它。
Now. Now we're in business.
现在。 现在我们在做生意。
Yeah, we'll get us hmm.
是的，我们会得到我们嗯。
I'm smart.
我很聪明。
Fucking smart, too.
还真他妈聪明。
Yeah.
是的。
Unfortunately, like, I.
不幸的是，像，我。
I was thinking a little bit too hard about it.
我有点想太多了。
Yeah.
是的。
All I had to do was just jump down the hole.
我所要做的就是跳下洞。
I completely forgot. Like,
我完全忘了。 就像，当它关闭时，它并没有关闭整个东西
like this looks dangerous.
像这样看起来很危险。
Because, you know, because it probably is dangerous.
因为，你知道，因为它可能很危险。
Shop also. Why the fuck do. You walk into the water?
购物也。 为什么他妈的。 你走进水里？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
How do I get over there without dying?
我如何在不死的情况下到达那里？
Jump.
跳。
Just jump.
跳吧。
Easy.
简单的。
Just jump hop.
只跳一跳。
I know.
我知道。
Then I jump far.
然后我跳得很远。
Enough on. Hop.
够了。 跳。
OK, there you go.
好的，给你。
I think I know I got you.
我想我知道我得到了你。
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
Now, that was good.
现在，那很好。
Oh, all the electricity in the in the apartment turned off, though.
哦，不过，公寓里所有的电都关掉了。
That sucks.
太糟糕了。
What was the point of that?
那有什么意义呢？
Oh, I just needed to get the stool.
哦，我只需要拿凳子。
I was over here.
我在这边。
All out for a goddamn stool.
为了一个该死的凳子而全力以赴。
OK, sure.
好的。
How many grannies have I killed?
我杀了多少奶奶？
I think now that was only the first one.
我想现在这只是第一个。
We've we've murdered
我们已经谋杀了
a row.
一排。
Row, and they got gonna make it more obvious.
行，他们会让它更明显。
I didn't know how to.
我不知道该怎么做。
Fall down into the dumpster.
掉进垃圾​​箱。
I miss my jump.
我想念我的跳跃。
I saw this TV off
我看到这台电视关了
I'll be like, I'm all distracted by it.
我会想，我都被它分心了。
Yeah, it's a lot of them.
是的，很多。
Let's just pretend like.
让我们假装喜欢。
Pretend like we don't see that move on with the saw.
假装我们没有看到锯子继续前进。
Next puzzle was this
下一个谜题是这个
is a shopping cart.
是一个购物车。
That's why anything from the grocery store
这就是为什么杂货店里的任何东西
my treat, I think
我的款待，我想，我想我去杂货店
today though to be honest, I have some stuff.
今天虽然老实说，我有一些东西。
In the water.
在水里。
What a gun really water electrocuted.
什么枪真的水电死了。
Bra oh no.
胸罩哦不。
I cannot get up there.
我爬不上去。
What's
什么是
where I'm stuck?
我被困在哪里？
Wait, I'm stuck.
等等，我卡住了。
I can't I can't move
我不能我不能移动以从卡住的地方获取原始的东西。
What I actually can't move, guys.
伙计们，我实际上无法移动。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Why? Why am I stuck here?
为什么？ 为什么我被困在这里？
How modern move
现代如何移动
all of roll.
所有的滚动。
OK, we start from checkpoint, please.
好的，请从检查站开始。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I don't know how
我不知道怎么
I know how.
我知道该怎样。
That is possible that we got, like, trapped in that scenario.
有可能我们被困在那种情况下。
But, hey, whatever happens, man,
但是，嘿，不管发生什么，伙计，
I think
我认为
I'll use the shopping cart this time rather than trying to use, like, dumb
这次我会使用购物车，而不是尝试使用，像，笨
dumb little
小笨蛋
what's it
它是什么
tricks?
技巧？
I wasn't even trying to.
我什至没有尝试。
Use a trick or like, speed or whatever.
使用技巧或类似，速度或其他任何东西。
I thought I could just jump over the legend, walk on top of that on ebay.
我以为我可以跳过这个传奇，在 ebay 上走在上面。
I can tell from here no OK.
从这里我可以看出不行。
Obviously, that's all I need to do.
显然，这就是我需要做的。
Now. The water's off
现在。 水没了
I need from here.
我需要从这里。
There's a wind up key
有一个发条钥匙
huh? Wait, what the fuck do I even pick up.
嗯？ 等等，我到底要捡什么东西。
All that ill?
都病了？
It's the fucking finale of toys.
这是玩具的他妈的结局。
Again from last time.
又是上次。
I hate those.
我讨厌那些。
Cod. They're so creepy.
鳕鱼。 他们是如此令人毛骨悚然。
I think it's the eye design for them
我认为是他们的眼睛设计真正为我做到了。
I guess the main reason why I don't like it
我猜我不喜欢它的主要原因
this feels weird.
这感觉很奇怪。
OK, so what does it mean?
好的，那是什么意思？
Turning off the power? Do
关掉电源？ 做
like I'm able to walk over here, ok?
就像我可以走过去一样，好吗？
All the TV is over the TV
所有的电视都在电视上
I'm going to come.
我要来了。
Please do not come
请不要来
can we cuddle?
我们可以拥抱吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Are you all
你们都是
I can treat me to dinner first.
我可以先请我吃饭。
I bring this down.
我把这个记下来。
Shopping cart
购物车
well, I can't wait. Why?
好吧，我等不及了。 为什么？
I cannot bring the shopping cart down bra.
我不能把购物车放下胸罩。
Oh, it doesn't want to go down
哦，它不想倒下
look at it.
看它。
Oh, now it's us.
哦，现在是我们。
I was weird.
我很奇怪。
Before.
前。
It was like it was being stuck on the on
就好像它被卡在了斜面上。
That's
这是一个非常愚蠢的确定。
Now wait.
现在等待。
Why was I was I not supposed to do that?
为什么我不应该那样做？
Blah, blah, blah.
等等等等等等。
I guess.
我猜。
I guess I had to use the cart.
我想我不得不使用购物车。
For what?
为了什么？
To get a TV, maybe? Is that it?
买个电视，可能吗？ 是这样吗？
Hmm. Uh,
唔。 呃，
all right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
I think I understand what I have to do now.
我想我明白我现在必须做什么了。
Once I turn the electricity back on
一旦我重新打开电源让电视工作，我就得停车按自己的方式停车。
So the shopping cart
所以购物车
right
对
and then I can turn the TV on
然后我可以打开电视然后去别的地方。
Easy peasy.
十分简单。
Nice. OK.
好的。 好的。
OK, you did it.
好的，你做到了。
Or is it going to bring us.
或者它会带给我们。
Oh, what the fuck are we going? Oh.
哦，我们他妈的要干什么？ 哦。
All the.
一切。
Why are there so many of you?
为什么你们这么多人？
Are they just doing their.
他们只是在做他们的。
They're just standing outside the fence like they're ready to horde me.
他们只是站在栅栏外，好像准备围攻我一样。
And I'll just
我会
let's just get away
让我们离开吧
about that.
关于那个。
Oh. Hmm.
哦。 唔。
Oh, I see.
我懂了。
OK, we turn it off.
好的，我们关掉它。
And then they're going to run down over here and break open the.
然后他们会跑到这里来破门而入。
Break.
休息。
Open the shop for me.
给我开店。
You know.
你知道。
We know.
我们知道。
They're not.
他们不是。
Oh, now we can all run in to the
哦，现在我们都可以跑到
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
oh, I'm sorry.
哦，对不起。
I'm sorry I interrupted your
对不起，我打断了你的卡通网络nickelodeon。
I don't know what you're watching.
我不知道你在看什么。
Please don't kill me.
请不要杀我。
You're in.
你在。
No, no.
不，不。
You told us to do that.
你告诉我们这样做。
You broke the TV.
你把电视弄坏了。
You fucking broke the TV.
你他妈把电视弄坏了。
Oh, I'm
哦，我要来了
yeah.
是的。
We are away from them first try.
我们是远离他们的第一次尝试。
I'd be happy about that, bro.
我会很高兴的，兄弟。
First try.
第一次尝试。
Zero deaths.
零死亡。
Oh, six.
哦，六个。
I'm going to get you out of there.
我要带你离开那里。
I'm gonna get you out of there.
我会带你离开那里。
But why is he going to come after me now?
可他现在为什么要来找我？
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow,
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔
ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔
There's an there's an. Oh, my God.
有一个有一个。 我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的天啊。 我的天啊。
Oh, my God. Oh, God. It's
我的天啊。 天啊。 它是
I did see the axe throw off
我确实看到斧头掉下来了
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦~
Please, please don't grab me.
请，请不要抓住我。
Please don't grab me. Please don't grab me. Give me a chance.
请不要抓住我。 请不要抓住我。 给我个机会。
Give me a chance. Oh, my God. Give me a chance.
给我个机会。 我的天啊。 给我个机会。
Holy shit.
天啊。
He you give me a chance.
他你给我一个机会。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Bobby's throwing.
鲍比的投掷。
Or maybe he's playing with me.
又或许他在和我玩。
Oh, he's right on top.
哦，他就在上面。
I see you.
我看见你。
I think he knows.
我想他知道。
I see him
我看见他
like he knows I'm around oh.
好像他知道我在身边哦。
Uh, Raul, uh.
呃，劳尔，呃。
You're creepy.
你很吓人。
That'd be a lot cooler for Dufus with a fedora.
对于戴软呢帽的杜弗斯来说，那会酷得多。
Well, no,
嗯，不，
I don't like that hallway.
我不喜欢那个走廊。
I don't like all that hallways looking right now.
我不喜欢现在看起来的所有走廊。
I don't like. It all, man.
我不喜欢。 这一切，伙计。
I don't like it. I don't like it.
我不喜欢它。 我不喜欢它。
I don't want it.
我不想要这个。
I don't want.
我不想。
I don't want it. I don't. Want it.
我不想要这个。 我不想要这个。 我不。 想要它。
I don't want it.
我不想要这个。
I don't want it
我不想要这个
why do you.
你为什么。
He teleports.
他传送。
He fucking teleports
他他妈的瞬移
did you see that shit?
你看到那个狗屎了吗？
Was he got to.
他有必要吗。
Teleport, man.
传送，伙计。
That's not fair.
这不公平。
We're on a train now.
我们现在在火车上。
I like that.
我喜欢。
It's pretty cool.
这很酷。
Oh, it's not cool anymore. It's not cool anymore.
哦，它不再酷了。 它不再酷了。
He's here.
他在这里。
How do you get here so fast?
你怎么这么快就到了？
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
my God. I think we're just.
我的上帝。 我认为我们是公正的。
We're just better. We're faster.
我们只是更好。 我们更快。
We're faster.
我们更快。
And better.
而且更好。
You know, ow.
你知道，哦。
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜呜呜呜
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
What?
什么？
Time.
时间。
Knock it away.
把它打掉。
What was that?
那是什么？
You saw the photos? I
你看到照片了吗？ 一世
I thought I got it.
我以为我明白了。
I flipped the switch and everything.
我拨动了开关和一切。
Oh, I had to flip even more.
哦，我不得不翻转更多。
OK, all right. Yes. Sucker
好的没问题。 是的。 吸盘
by loser
通过失败者
yeah.
是的。
Plan life
规划人生
speaking of trains, thanks for the hype.
说到火车，谢谢你的炒作。
Train one.
训练一个。
Oh, what a great sign.
哦，多么伟大的标志。
So I'll say thank you for that.
所以我会说谢谢你。
I've train over on the train six
我在六号火车上已经结束了
why do we still see six
为什么我们仍然看到六个来指导我
or trying to guide me to.
或试图引导我。
I'm supposed to go
我应该去
on now.
现在开始。
I'm fucked up
我完蛋了
he looks really hurt.
他看起来真的很受伤。
Mano, you OK?
马诺，你好吗？
You're not going to die on. Me, right?
你不会死的。 我，对吧？
I ask.
我问。
Do the parallels on this reminds me of, like, when we were playing the first game,
这方面的相似之处让我想起了，比如，当我们玩第一场比赛时，
like, walking down the aisle to the exit i sex just sucking
就像，沿着过道走到出口我做爱只是吸吮灵魂和东西。
Sex is a girl.
性是一个女孩。
I mean, I call everyone bro or dude, regardless of
我的意思是，我称每个人都是兄弟或伙计，无论
if you're a girl or not.
如果你是一个女孩或不是。
It's gender neutral.
它是性别中立的。
It's nothing new.
这不是什么新鲜事。
I've done it all the time.
我一直都这样做。
Yeah,
是的，
I'm really worried right now.
我现在真的很担心。
Like he's not going to die right?
好像他不会死吧？
Why we took our hat off her paper bag.
为什么我们从她的纸袋上摘下帽子。
Hat off
脱帽致敬
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
We're about to have our anime.
我们即将有我们的动漫。
Moments.
时刻。
But the clock.
但是时钟。
Show, it's a psychic battle.
显示，这是一场心灵的战斗。
It's like that show.
就像那个节目一样。
You see a mob psycho.
你看到一个暴民心理。
All the time.
每时每刻。
We're winning.
我们正在获胜。
Why the fuck are we.
为什么我们是他妈。
Winning, though?
还是赢了？
Why you dead.
为什么你死了。
He started.
他开始。
To fucking kill them.
去他妈的杀了他们。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Lam controlling the city.
林控城。
OK, Mano
好的，马诺
OK, Mano.
好的，马诺。
You're pretty strong.
你很强壮。
Oh, I can't.
哦，我不能。
I want to see his face
我想看看他的脸
That's impossible.
那是不可能的。
It's not going to let me, though, is it?
不过，它不会让我这么做的，不是吗？
Now? I can't see anything
现在？ 我什么都看不见
yeah.
是的。
All right.
好的。
I'm gonna go get six back.
我要去拿六回。
Yeah, I go save our friend.
是的，我去救我们的朋友。
That's the last thing.
那是最后一件事。
We killed the weird soul guy.
我们杀了那个奇怪的灵魂家伙。
With the fedora who kind of reminds me of Frank Sinatra.
带着有点让我想起弗兰克辛纳屈的软呢帽。
But he's.
但他是。
He doesn't. He's not Frank's.
他没有。 他不是弗兰克的。
Dude, you know, he kind of does.
伙计，你知道，他有点像。
Remind me of him minus the, you know, the super powers
让我想起他减去你知道的超能力。 是的，
like a psycho,
像个精神病，像某种邪恶
technology obsessed
像 Sinatra 一样痴迷于技术。
So just sucker.
所以只是傻逼。
So on to his TV world.
等到他的电视世界。
And never stop singing Fly Me to the Moon.
永远不要停止唱《Fly Me to the Moon》。
And New York.
还有纽约。
Is not a song that he sang.
不是他唱的歌。
Didn't he sing like
他不是唱的像
I wanna be part of it?
我想成为其中的一员？
New York.
纽约。
Something like that.
类似的东西。
Right.
对。
As I say, this world is really fucking cool.
正如我所说，这个世界真的很酷。
This is the same music from the first game.
这与第一场比赛的音乐相同。
Oh, well,
那好吧，
a lot
很多
I'm lagging.
我落后了。
I don't think I'm lagging. Everything seems fine.
我不认为我落后。 一切似乎都很好。
Just refresh your browser. On
只需刷新您的浏览器。 在
I think I got follow the music right
我想我听音乐是对的
right.
对。
That seems to be the trick about this.
这似乎是关于这个的伎俩。
We follow the where the music goes
我们跟随音乐的去向
seems easy enough
似乎很容易
and we'll head towards us, I think.
我想我们会朝我们走来。
But what it's.
但它是什么。
All the purple.
都是紫色的。
And pink, it just looks so goddamn pretty
粉红色的，它看起来真他妈的漂亮
it's a little it's a bit eerie.
有点怪怪的。
So Plotz Barney runs this whole thing.
所以 Plotz Barney 负责整个事情。
God, no, please.
上帝，不，请。
A fork. No,
一把叉子。 不，
I never want to hear anything
我再也不想听到那只紫色恐龙的声音了。
Are these doors not hmm.
这些门不是嗯。
Here we go.
开始了。
How I.
我怎么。
I supposed to get inside, though?
不过，我应该进去吗？
Following me inside the door.
跟着我进了门。
You had to push this one open.
你必须把这个推开。
I should push it open.
我应该把它推开。
Push it, push it open.
推，推开。
Ah. OK.
啊。 好的。
So instead, use the axe. We.
因此，请使用斧头。 我们。
I don't see an axe around. Here is your knocks.
我没有看到周围有斧头。 这是你的敲门声。
Yeah.
是的。
Was just a really heavy door.
只是一扇很重的门。
God knows why
天知道为什么
although I hope everyone here is having a great morning
尽管我希望到目前为止，这里的每个人都度过了一个愉快的早晨，并检查了所有这些。
Yes. Taking care of yourselves.
是的。 照顾好自己。
Everything's chill.
一切都凉了。
These good,
这些好，
very cosy, very comfy.
很温馨，很舒服。
You got breakfast, dinner,
你有早餐，晚餐，有一个很好的饮料，也许是小吃。
Said milk. Nice
说牛奶。 好的
I think people or I do enjoy drinking.
我认为人们或我确实喜欢喝酒。
Just straight up milk.
直接加牛奶就好了。
No, from a couple.
不，来自一对夫妇。
I don't think that's bad.
我不认为那是坏事。
I know some people think it's weird
我知道有些人认为将其推低是很奇怪的。
I think we need.
我认为我们需要。
We need to. You. Let's come back over here.
我们要。 你。 让我们回到这里。
Not side
不是侧面
Z today.
今天Z。
Yeah, I had pancakes today.
是的，我今天吃了煎饼。
I had pancakes and sausage and eggs.
我吃了煎饼、香肠和鸡蛋。
Is really delicious.
真的很好吃。
It's been
自从我吃煎饼以来已经过去了，所以我真的很开心
any day I have pancakes is a good day.
我吃煎饼的任何一天都是美好的一天。
Here we are married
我们在这里结婚了
I always.
我总是。
I think we made it oh.
我想我们成功了哦。
Wow. Six
哇。 六
here.
这里。
You look a little different.
你看起来有点不同。
Sex did you are. Did you get a manicure?
你是性的。 你修指甲了吗？
Get a haircut, I think.
理发吧，我觉得
Yeah. Haircut. You've.
是的。 理发。 你有。
Have you been eating more?
你吃得更多了吗？
I know something of value
我知道有价值的东西似乎有点不同。
I think.
我认为。
I think you got a haircut.
我想你理发了。
I be sure you show me.
我确定你给我看。
Would you show me your music box now? OK.
你现在可以给我看看你的音乐盒吗？ 好的。
Oh, prosecutor call
哦，检察官电话
me. Yes.
我。 是的。
I can't really see his face.
我真的看不清他的脸。
It's all covered up.
这一切都被掩盖了。
But up
但是起来
on the hill.
山坡上。
Oh, all right.
哦那好吧。
That's a break. The box.
那是休息。 盒子。
I don't want him.
我不要他。
She's going to get pissed at us.
她会生我们的气的。
Hey, buddy.
你好朋友。
Buddy, I'm going to.
哥们，我去
I'm going to do something.
我要做点什么。
You come over here and don't look all right?
你过来看看不好吗？
I know all about all of you.
我知道你们所有人。
Just don't all.
只是不要全部。
Fuck it, bro. OK, whatever.
去他妈的，兄弟。 好吧，随你便。
I guess we have to
我想我们必须
let's just say sorry.
让我们说对不起。
All I know say sorry now.
我现在只知道说对不起。
Sorry.
对不起。
Hey. What
嘿。 什么
oh, oh, no.
哦，哦，不。
Oh, no, no, no. Oh, no. They'll run.
哦，不，不，不。 不好了。 他们会跑。
I run and run the fuck away.
我跑了，他妈的跑了。
Just mad piss.
简直是狂尿。
Just piss
只是小便
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉。 我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. Oh, bro.
我很抱歉。 我很抱歉。 哦，兄弟。
Oh, no, no, no, no. I'm sorry. Six.
哦，不，不，不，不，不。 对不起。 六。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
Don't kill me.
不要杀我。
No, I died.
不，我死了。
Oh, he died.
哦，他死了。
She didn't kill. Me.
她没有杀人。 我。
I made my own death.
我自己死了。
Perception kills. Me.
知觉杀人。 我。
Hey. Hey, how about how about this?
嘿。 嘿，这个怎么样？
All right, how about after this?
好吧，那之后呢？
We we can go to McDonald's together, all right?
我们可以一起去麦当劳，好吗？
We can get.
我们可以得到。
I'll buy you the spicy chicken nuggets.
我给你买辣鸡块。
You know, they came. Those came back earlier.
你知道，他们来了。 那些早回来了。
Yeah, I can buy you some spicy chicken nuggets.
是的，我可以给你买些辣鸡块。
Please, please don't hurt me
请，请不要伤害我
and the McFlurry.
和麦旋风。
I'll get you a McFlurry.
我会给你一个麦旋风。
Oh, what.
啊什么。
Do you like? My place
你喜欢？ 我的地方
all thorough.
一切彻底。
I'll throw now.
我现在就扔。
I'll throw in some apple slices.
我会放一些苹果片。
Still
仍然
why do you look so creepy?
为什么你看起来那么可怕？
Look so goddamn creepy?
长得这么吓人？
OK, oh, he.
好的，哦，他。
Acts.
行动。
I see that face right there.
我看到那张脸就在那里。
His goddamn weird
他这该死的怪人
yeah.
是的。
Her arm is really creeping me out.
她的手臂真的让我毛骨悚然。
I don't like how her arm looks
我不喜欢她手臂的样子
the fucking water from
他妈的水
this. Oh.
这。 哦。
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿。
No, I was too small.
不，我太小了。
Tell it.
告诉它。
Ok? I think I see why, guys, you know,
好的？ 我想我明白为什么了，伙计们，你们知道，
I should call her and then jump into the portal
我应该打电话给她然后跳进传送门
and then go over there
然后去那里
the other two.
另外两个。
Slow there.
那里慢。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Nice job, mano.
干得好，马诺。
Is it that we keep going, though?
是我们继续前进吗？
It's like we transport ourselves into another dimension for a second.
就像我们将自己传送到另一个维度一秒钟。
Wow. Oh,
哇。 哦，
oh. Where the fuck are we?
哦。 我们他妈在哪里？
There's another door here.
这里还有一扇门。
Lots of breaking open doors with axes.
许多用斧头打开的门。
Is this like, is it because this is how we first met sex like,
是这样吗，是不是因为这是我们第一次遇到性的方式，
remember back in the house, we, like, broke down the door, like,
记得回到房子里，我们，就像，打破了门，就像，
hey, let me ask you a question.
嘿，让我问你一个问题。
Is it like trying to remind us of.
是不是想提醒我们。
That or something?
那还是什么？
Hard that's really good.
硬是真的很好。
Yeah.
是的。
I feel like that's the reason why
我觉得这就是为什么
we keep seeing the door break and stuff.
我们不断看到门破之类的东西。
Go, hello.
去吧，你好。
And get some more water oh,
多喝点水哦
a quick water break because
快速断水，因为
I didn't drink water a little bit
我没有喝一点水
I keep my lips moist.
我保持嘴唇湿润。
And my and my throat lubricated.
我和我的喉咙都润滑了。
Of course.
当然。
It's just more doors, more.
只是更多的门，更多。
Doors open, doors open, doors open, doors open, doors
开门，开门，开门，开门，开门，开门
again.
再次。
Who is my axe?
谁是我的斧头？
Oh, there it is.
哦，是的。
Oh, can I get my axe back?
哦，我可以拿回我的斧头吗？
I oh, my God.
我哦，我的上帝。
How am I supposed to grab that shit?
我该怎么去抓那个狗屎？
Fuck shit.
他妈的狗屎。
I got smashed like a bargain.
我像讨价还价一样被砸了。
Fuck me.
操我。
Fuck me. No, no.
操我。 不，不。
Oh, dude, wait.
哦，伙计，等等。
I think I see why.
我想我明白为什么了。
Guys, you go.
伙计们，你们走吧。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
No, Raul, I
不，劳尔，我
I died after I walked through the portal.
我穿过传送门后就死了。
How No, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. OK,
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。 好的，
nice.
好的。
Oh, now.
哦，现在。
That one was a little tricky.
那个有点棘手。
A little bit a little bit trickier.
有点棘手。
I'm sorry. Sex.
对不起。 性别。
Let me get up to you after after this is over, ok?
等这件事结束后让我来找你，好吗？
God, she's back.
天啊，她回来了。
She's back.
她回来了。
Oh, she's back.
哦，她回来了。
You're not you, and you're hungry.
你不是你，你饿了。
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
哦，操。 哦，操。
Of the entire place is breaking down.
整个地方都在崩溃。
What is that?
那是什么？
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, God. Sex, sex.
天啊。 性，性。
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿嘿嘿。
I want to help me.
我想帮助我。
I'm a bit I'm the lost world where we are.
我有点我是我们所在的迷失世界。
And why that? What is that? What?
为什么？ 那是什么？ 什么？
Why is it drawn to Jesus word?
为什么会被耶稣的话所吸引？
Is this a tower thing?
这是塔的事吗？
Why is it tower looks so fucking.
为什么它的塔看起来这么他妈的。
Weird for
很奇怪
I don't know.
我不知道。
I know
我知道
please,
请，
please.
请。
Sex sex
性爱
oh, emotional damage.
哦，精神伤害。
Fuck you.
去你的。
I knew I was going.
我知道我要走了。
I knew somebody was going to do that.
我知道有人会这样做。
Oh, why
哦为什么
oh, I yell back.
哦，我喊回来。
Stabs, brawl. Mm.
刺，打架。 毫米。
No, we're stuck in the goop.
不，我们陷入了困境。
It looks like it looks like a brain
它看起来像一个大脑
I can't even see my face either.
我什至看不到我的脸。
Still
仍然
I was cold as fuck.
我冷得要死。
It was cold
天很冷
I don't know why she did it.
我不知道她为什么这样做。
Still
仍然
where we're going.
我们要去哪里。
She's a lover.
她是一个情人。
She has a lover or not a lover.
她有情人或没有情人。
I mean, are we all over
我的意思是，我们都结束了吗
we kind of.
我们有点。
We're alive.
我们活着。
But I don't know how alive.
但我不知道怎么活。
I stop on the I it's so fucking creepy.
我停下来，这太他妈的令人毛骨悚然了。
Yeah,
是的，
whose eyes are those?
那是谁的眼睛？
What are you.
你是做什么的。
Oh. I can't walk.
哦。 我不能走路。
I'm stuck
我被困住了
chilling here.
在这里不寒而栗。
By myself, and I'll have sex.
一个人，我会做爱。
Say more, my friend.
多说一句，我的朋友。
I just have that weird eye monster.
我只有那个奇怪的眼睛怪物。
We're getting older.
我们正在变老。
A lot older.
年纪大了。
On how much time is passed or if this is, like, happening
关于经过了多少时间，或者这是否正在发生
really quickly.
真的很快。
Oh, oh, yeah.
哦，哦，是的。
We got we got a Frank Sinatra.
我们得到了弗兰克·辛纳屈。
No. No.
不，不。
This entire time, we were the hot man.
一直以来，我们都是炙手可热的人。
I don't completely understand it, but I
我不完全理解，但我
we're just him.
我们只是他。
That's us.
那就是我们。
I know why I like
我知道为什么我喜欢我们是个令人毛骨悚然的家伙，但同时，你喜欢
that bird from the TV and.
电视里的那只鸟和。
Shit, but ok.
妈的，不过还好。
And that's it.
就是这样。
Michael Jackson.
迈克尔杰克逊。
Shut up.
住口。
Moves on.
继续前进。
Oh. We kiss more
哦。 我们亲吻更多
there's more. Wow.
还有更多。 哇。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
All right. Six escapes.
好的。 六逃。
Hey, how's it feel to be a trader, huh?
嘿，当交易员的感觉如何，对吧？
How's it feel.
感觉如何。
To be a cold hearted fucking backstabbing
做一个冷酷无情的背叛叛徒？ 性别
what are you hungry?
你饿什么？
Yeah, right.
是的，对。
That's
从字面上看，这就是小噩梦的下一部分的开始。
One I think
一个我认为
she gets that never ending hunger
她得到了永无止境的饥饿感
oh, wow. Wow.
哦，哇。 哇。
This game.
这个游戏。
Gives me. Chills every single time.
给我。 每次都发冷。
It gives me so much chills just thinking about that conclusion.
光是想到这个结论，就让我不寒而栗。
It's so fucking cool. Man.
太他妈酷了 男人。
This game is really good.
这个游戏真的很好。
It's really fucking good. I think.
它真的很好。 我认为。
I think I'm willing to say it's better.
我想我愿意说它更好。
It's one of the rare times, like the
这是罕见的时期之一，就像续集确实比原版更好。
It's. It's like some degrees, right?
它的。 这就像一些学位，对吧？
Because there's just a lot more content
因为有更多的内容更多的故事，喜欢
the spooks are spookier
幽灵更可怕
like all numbers one is also like really good too.
像所有的数字一样，第一也非常好。
But this is like you know they outdid themselves the one
但这就像你知道他们超越了自己
they really did outdid themselves
他们确实超越了自己
so the honest lesson
所以诚实的教训
is it really.
真的吗。
And that.
然后。
Was little nightmares till
是小噩梦直到
we're going to move on to our next game.
我们将继续进行下一场比赛。
Don't go anywhere because I'm about to move on so home sweet home.
不要去任何地方，因为我要继续前进所以回家甜蜜的家。
Next.
下一个。
Yeah.
是的。
That's our next game with the night we're finishing
那是我们结束之夜的下一场比赛
I'm not going to. Go anywhere. Just yet. We got another game.
我不会。 去任何地方。 刚刚。 我们有另一场比赛。
Because again, like I said, I really want to finish home sweet home
因为再一次，就像我说的，我真的很想完成回家甜蜜的家
and see a
并看到一个
see the conclusions of that game as well, since we have like two more hours
看看那场比赛的结论，因为我们离俄克拉荷马城的主场还有两个小时，我认为是对的。
God, I can't wait.
天哪，我等不及了。
Dude, I've been thinking about it all day yesterday.
哥们，昨天我一直在想这件事。
The Short by Bandai
万代的短片
you can skip this.
你可以跳过这个。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Yeah, actually, I'll,
是的，实际上，我会，
I'll see you through the entire credits.
我会看到你通过整个学分。
In the meantime, on
与此同时，在
we should do I miss the lady?
我们应该想念那位女士吗？
No, I honestly fuck the she is creepy.
不，我老实说她他妈的令人毛骨悚然。
She is soul guards down creepy man.
她是一个令人毛骨悚然的灵魂守卫者。
The box cutter.
切盒机。
I don't even know that was box cutter.
我什至不知道那是切盒机。
I thought it was a screwdriver.
我还以为是螺丝刀
That's why I like click so much like
这就是为什么我非常喜欢点击
that. She's just, like, moving it up and down.
那。 她只是，就像，上下移动它。
Up and down.
上和下。
For some reason, I thought it was a screwdriver in her hand,
不知为何，我还以为是她手里的螺丝刀，好像是她在敲
the little nightmares,
小噩梦，两个游戏团队，制作人，执行团队。
They did a great job, and I hope they make a little nightmare story.
他们做得很好，我希望他们能创造一个噩梦般的故事。
I feel like they will.
我觉得他们会的。
There's so much like, you know, good feedback for low numbers, too.
你知道，对于低数字也有很好的反馈。
I don't like why wouldn't they make a number three, right?
我不喜欢他们为什么不打三号，对吧？
And maybe they can make a multiplayer
也许他们可以制作多人游戏
I think they can do it
我认为他们可以做到
and make me really happy.
让我真的很开心。
Maybe it doesn't have to be a six, but it could be a different like
也许它不必是六，但它可能是不同的
set of characters
字符集
and just getting to play a multiplayer for this kind of game would be really cool,
为这种游戏玩多人游戏真的很酷，
cool for Friend, and I really hope that they consider doing that.
对朋友来说很酷，我真的希望他们考虑这样做。
Like at least have it as an option to do multiplayer
至少可以将其作为多人游戏的选择
Oh. I've ever played Puppy Playtime.
哦。 我曾经玩过Puppy Playtime。
I heard Chapter two for the game came out, but I'm not sure
听说游戏第二章出来了，不知道要不要做
because I don't know if
因为不知道喜不喜欢他们还是不知道喜不喜欢，
you know, ideal
你知道，理想
I'll think about it, I'll think about it because like not sure
我会考虑一下，我会考虑一下，因为不确定支持者是否仍然喜欢，你知道，做
NFC and stuff
NFC之类的
or like the creators of the company mature.
或者像公司的创造者一样成熟。
That's a look into that and see what's up.
那就是调查一下，看看发生了什么。
If not, then OK, maybe I'll consider playing it, but we'll see
如果没有，那么好吧，也许我会考虑玩它，但我们会看到
OK, now give me a second, y'all.
好的，现在给我一秒钟，你们大家。
I'm going to quickly uh,
我要赶紧呃，
quickly announce on the server that we're going to transition over
很快在服务器上宣布我们将要过渡它是甜蜜的家，因为我认为有些人想为那场比赛被
it's home sweet home because I think some people want to be pinged for that game
ping
I like for a bit because I'm, I'm tabbed out.
我有点喜欢，因为我是，我被淘汰了。
At. Everyone
在。 每个人
moving.
移动。
It's a home sweet home now.
现在是一个温馨的家。
We finished little nightmares still.
我们仍然完成了小小的噩梦。
So now we're going to move on to our second
所以现在我们将继续我们的第二个
game of the nights and finish that off for today.
晚上的游戏，并在今天完成它。
See, as soon
快来看看
OK, OK.
好的好的。
I think I think that one thorough
我想我认为一个彻底
all right.
好的。
But in the meantime, so you guys should probably
但与此同时，你们应该去给自己买点零食和饮料吧，对吧？
But let me see.
但是让我看看。
There's no place.
没有地方。
Like home
像家
is no place like home.
没有像家一样的地方。
There's no place like home.
金窝银窝不如自己家里的狗窝。
Pass it home sweet
把它带回家甜蜜
home. OK,
家。 好的，
close out of that, OK?
关闭它，好吗？
Yeah. Well, thank you, guys.
是的。 嗯，谢谢各位。
For watching through a little nightmares ,too.
也可以通过一些噩梦来观看。
We're going to be moving on to our next game.
我们将继续我们的下一场比赛。
So where is Home Sweet Home?
那么甜蜜的家在哪里？
where the fuck is it?
他妈的在哪里？
Hello?
你好？
Is really nice getting
真的很高兴能够像这样让自己焕然一新并再次经历整个冒险。
So thanks for
所以谢谢你
coming by and being patient
路过并耐心等待，
with me as well.
和我一起。
You know, like bought up some puzzles.
你知道，就像买了一些拼图一样。
Oh my God.
我的天啊。
Here we go again.
又来了。
Here we fucking go.
我们他妈的走吧。
I thought.
我想。
Wait. One more thing I forgot to do.
等待。 还有一件事我忘了做。
Let me check , ah
让我查一下，啊
And let me check
让我检查一下
this caught one more time, and then we should be fine.
这又抓到了一次，然后我们应该会没事的。
And look,
看，
I totally recommend, like, if you've never
我完全推荐，如果你以前从来没有玩过小噩梦，对吧？
Like the first one.
和第一个一样。
And this is like your first introduction to this series,
这就像你对这个系列的第一次介绍，
you should definitely consider
您绝对应该考虑自己玩第一个或自己玩第二个。
If you liked what you saw and support the game
如果你喜欢你所看到的并支持游戏
All right.
好的。
It's puzzles time.
现在是拼图时间。
All Are proposing give a donation.
所有人都在提议捐款。
Who who donated
谁捐了
hey nora thank you for the 5000 bits and oni thank you for the 5000 gift subs
嘿，诺拉，谢谢你的 5000 比特，我感谢你的
and thenying thank you for the 01 and
5000 礼物潜艇，然后感谢你的 01 和
are gio thank you for another ten gift subs as well and make
是 gio 也感谢您提供另外十个礼物潜艇，并感谢您的
thanks for the 1000 bits and jack thank you for the 1000 bits
1000 位和杰克感谢您的 1000 位
so much guys
这么多家伙
OK so
好的
I think we can continue or do chapter select
我想我们可以继续或做章节选择
hopeless circle the nightmare begins.
无望的圆圈噩梦开始了。
Oh am I missing something.
哦，我错过了什么。
It says I'm missing. A collectable item or whatever.
它说我失踪了。 收藏品什么的。
OK I said and finding whatever that was
好的，我说并找到了任何东西
do I want to continue or do
我想继续还是做
I want to start from hopeless circle
我要从绝望的圈子开始
or continue
或继续
I think it's saved everything.
我认为它保存了一切。
Right?
对？
We'll see.
我们拭目以待。
Oh yeah, it does.
哦，是的，确实如此。
Oh, well, no, I hear again.
哦，好吧，不，我又听到了。
Oh, I fucking hear her again.
哦，我他妈的又听到她的声音了。
Jesus,
耶稣，
the bump up the volume a little bit
稍微提高音量，然后直接进入这个烂摊子。
The cutter sound.
刀声。
Yeah, OK.
是的，好的。
The guys remember what we have to do.
伙计们记得我们必须做什么。
What's our objective here?
我们在这里的目标是什么？
Do we follow the
我们是否遵循
the strings?
字符串？
Right?
对？
She there?
她在吗？
Oh, no.
不好了。
We follow the string.
我们跟随字符串。
Where is the string lead us?
绳子把我们引向何方？
it's going to there's
它会到这里有一些绳子。
Oh, man.
天啊。
Wow. Oh, no.
哇。 不好了。
Na na na na na, bro.
呐呐呐呐呐，兄弟。
Well, what is
那么，什么是
oh. Shit.
哦。 拉屎。
OK, we're out on more.
好的，我们还有更多。
My God.
我的上帝。
All right.
好的。
I guess we'll maybe we can just find the one over here
我想我们也许可以在这里找到那个，因为她在那个地区。
All right, let's follow the string here first,
好吧，我们先按照这里的字符串，
see where it goes.
看看它去哪里。
There's no way she's going to show up here, right?
她不可能出现在这里，对吧？
Right.
对。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
I have the key for it.
我有它的钥匙。
Now, why does the source.
现在，为什么来源。
Lock fuck
锁他妈的
know she showed off from the portal
知道她在门户网站上炫耀
ah
啊
That's
那是
all right.
好的。
All right, we're good. We're good.
好吧，我们很好。 我们很好。
Go. Up
去。 向上
oh, I'm.
哦，我是。
Screwed. I'm so screwed. I'm so screwed.
搞砸了。 我真搞砸了。 我真搞砸了。
I am so fucking screwed.
我真他妈的搞砸了。
Ah.
啊。
Uh guys, guys, guys.
伙计们，伙计们，伙计们。
This alone.
仅此而已。
I don't think the demon was going to be there to
我不认为恶魔会在那里
who was that face was.
那张脸是谁。
Can somebody translate
有人可以翻译吗
you motherfucker
你个混蛋
Maybe me turn off sound alerts again.
也许我再次关闭声音警报。
I'll do it.
我会做的。
I swear to God, I'll do it.
我向上帝发誓，我会做到的。
It's over here.
它在这里。
I don't know where I'm following the
我不知道我在哪里跟随弦乐
we're just going to wait.
我们只是等待。
I'll be patient.
我会耐心的。
Oh, no.
不好了。
I don't want to come.
我不想来。
No, no, come.
不不不，来吧。
No. Coming back.
不，回来。
No.
不。
Oh. Look away, please.
哦。 请移开视线。
Look away, please. So I can go.
请移开视线。 这样我就可以走了。
So I can run
所以我可以跑
I think.
我认为。
God god. Oh,
神神。 哦，还有更多。
There's more
还有更多
she can come behind oh,
她可以跟在后面哦，
my God.
我的上帝。
There's so many beings everywhere.
到处都有这么多的生命。
I'm paranoid, man.
我是偏执狂，伙计。
I think we're fine.
我认为我们很好。
I just got to take it slowly.
我只好慢慢来。
Take it nice and slow. Nice and slow , shoto.
慢慢来。 好又慢，shoto。
All right? There's no need to rush anything.
好的？ 没有必要急于求成。
You just got to be more patient sometimes
有时你只需要多一点耐心
I don't even want to go down there just yet.
我什至还不想去那里。
You just come back around.
你只是回来。
Oh, don't do that.
哦，不要那样做。
Arsehole. Oh.
混蛋。 哦。
Please look away.
请移开视线。
Please look away, fuck
请移开视线，他妈的
I hate this so much.
我非常讨厌这个。
I hate this so much. I'm stuck
我非常讨厌这个。 我被困住了
ohh ahh, it's very nerve wracking, man.
啊啊啊，真是伤脑筋，伙计。
I don't like it.
我不喜欢它。
ohh,
哦，
at least there's lockers in height.
至少有储物柜的高度。
He's looking at me.
他正在看着我。
That fucker is looking at me right now.
那个混蛋现在正看着我。
Do you see that?
你看到了吗？
I can't leave
我不能离开
she is unpog. hh
她没有生气。 呵呵
I like that.
我喜欢。
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜呜呜呜
How how am I supposed to
我该如何通过那里？
We're good for good
我们永远好
we're fine?
我们都很好？
We're fine.
我们都很好。
Well, wait.
嗯，等等。
What am I supposed to do here?
我应该在这里做什么？
What's my goal?
我的目标是什么？
What's my goal in this place?
我在这个地方的目标是什么？
And is she coming?
她会来吗？
Oh, she's coming.
哦，她来了。
The candle .
蜡烛 。
Did I miss the candle.
我错过了蜡烛吗？
I think that I've missed the candle already.
我想我已经错过了蜡烛。
It's on. I love you.
它开着。 我爱你。
I don't know you. Who are you? What's.
我不认识你。 你是谁？ 什么是。
Who the fuck are you? What do you mean, I ? I love you.
你他妈是谁？ 你什么意思，我？ 我爱你。
Where are the candles, man?
蜡烛在哪里，伙计？
Turn around.
回转。
Nice. don't.
好的。 不。
Emotional  Damage.
情感伤害。
I hate you.
我恨你。
I hate you guys.
我讨厌你们。
Stop.
停止。
Stop with the sound alerts.
停止声音警报。
I'm going to cry.
我要哭了。
You're gonna make me cry.
你会让我哭的。
Where's the candles?
蜡烛在哪里？
There's, like, you guys always together.
就像，你们永远在一起。
Where's candles Where's candles.
蜡烛在哪里 蜡烛在哪里。
Where's the candles.
蜡烛在哪里。
I don't know where the candles are.
我不知道蜡烛在哪里。
Oh, oh. Yes.
哦，哦。 是的。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
That's bad.
那很不好。
OK, I don't mind.
好吧，我不介意。
Like, if I pass by the candles.
就像，如果我经过蜡烛。
Well, you know, if I pass by it, cause I have no idea
好吧，你知道，如果我经过它，因为我不知道
where the fuck they are.
他们他妈的在哪里。
I mean, I might have seen already.
我的意思是，我可能已经看过了。
Did I see the kid?
我看到那个孩子了吗？
Tell me I.
告诉我我。
See the candles already.
已经看到蜡烛了。
Like, I just passed by it or something.
比如，我只是路过它什么的。
You? No.
你？ 不。
I didn't
我没有
Won't pass that.
不会通过的。
I really
我真的
fuck yes.
他妈的是的。
Oh, there it is.
哦，是的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
There it is. What?
它在那里。 什么？
We were right there before.
我们之前就在那里。
OK, poof.
好的，噗。
There goes the candle.
蜡烛去了。
Poggers
波格斯
hello now.
现在你好。
Oh. Oh, oh.
哦。 哦，哦。
help someone help? Oh.
帮助某人帮助？ 哦。
Excuse oh.
对不起哦。
This is bad.
这是不好的。
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
shit.
拉屎。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Get out of here, man.
离开这里，伙计。
You want to save me?
你想救我吗？
Then why are you stabbing me for box cutter. Huh?
那你为什么要刺我切盒机。 嗯？
I don't think that's saving me. I think.
我不认为那是在拯救我。 我认为。
I think that's trying to kill me.
我认为那是想杀了我。
I think you have a very different idea
我觉得你对救我的想法很不一样。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Bull fucking shit
他妈的狗屎她想救我。 好的？
The candles been burned
蜡烛被烧了
that's one down.
那是一个下来。
We got one candle.
我们得到了一根蜡烛。
Now what .
怎么办 。
It was back here
它回到了这里
a piece of a mysterious photograph.
一张神秘的照片。
And boxes.
和盒子。
I made it,
我做到了，但我们还有更多的蜡烛要烧。
Yeah, I'll go find them.
是的，我会去找他们的。
It's not over.
它还没有结束。
Shit. here it is. OK.
拉屎。 这里是。 好的。
Wait, is there another room?
等等，还有房间吗？
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Is there more?
还有更多吗？
But we?
但我们？
Well, we burned it already, didn't we?
好吧，我们已经把它烧掉了，不是吗？
Is there another candle in there?
里面还有蜡烛吗？
Are is there another candle in here that we have to burn?
这里有没有另一根蜡烛需要我们烧掉？
I don't know.
我不知道。
There is ? Fuck.
有 ？ 他妈的。
All in the different rooms.
都在不同的房间。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
Please. Sorry.
请。 对不起。
I don't want to burn the candle again.
我不想再烧蜡烛了。
Emotional damage.
情感伤害。
God, she's fast. Man.
上帝，她很快。 男人。
I hate how fast she is.
我讨厌她的速度。
I'm going to go check.
我要去检查一下。
I think.
我认为。
I think we have to burn it again.
我认为我们必须再次烧毁它。
Fuck bro.
去他妈的兄弟。
Oh, oh, my.
哦，哦，我的。
God. I ran into her. Oops. Oops.
上帝。 我撞到了她。 哎呀。 哎呀。
I didn't mean to do that.
我不是故意的。 我不是故意的。
Well,
好，
what!
什么！
Off This is hard, man.
关闭 这很难，伙计。
This is hard.
这很难。
How did she find me?
她是怎么找到我的？
I was crouched down and everything was OK because she saw me walk.
我蹲下来，一切都很好，因为她看到我走路。
into the locker
进储物柜
ok. OK, ok.
行。 好的好的。
We got it this time.
这次我们明白了。
You're cringe.
你在畏缩。
Hey, you lady.
嘿，你这个女士。
This was not
这不是我应该去的地方。
I'm. I'm hiding this time
我是。 这次我躲起来了，所以你看不见我，对吧？ 哦。
How, how,
怎么样，怎么样，怎么样，不。
Bro, I,
兄弟，我，我走出储物柜，他已经准备好了
on my arse.
在我的屁股上。
Okay.Should I
好的，我要等他吗？
wait for him.
转过来
a few moments later,
片刻之后，
come on.
来吧。
Turn, turn already.
转，已经转了。
Cringe, cringe, cringe,
畏缩，畏缩，畏缩，畏缩，畏缩。
Now that's one candle.
现在那是一根蜡烛。
Is there another candle in here?
这里还有一根蜡烛吗？
Somebody please help me, because I'm not sure if there's another one or not.
有人请帮助我，因为我不确定是否还有另一个。
Hmm? Somebody
唔？ 有人告诉我，这个房间里还有一根蜡烛吗？
Inside this room?
这个房间里面？
I know there's other candles
我知道像我们必须关注的其他领域一样，还有其他蜡烛，所以。
But is there more here?
但是这里还有更多吗？
I think that was it right
我认为那是对的
oh, that's it.
哦，就是这样。
Then why did I come back here? I
那我为什么又回到了这里？ 一世
bullshit, bullshit, bullshit.
废话，废话，废话。
Then I got trolled.
然后我被拖了。
I got trolled.
我上当了。
Somebody said that there was another.
有人说还有一个。
One in here, and I believe them.
一个在这里，我相信他们。
Let's just wait for it to go out, and.
让我们等它出去，然后。
And then we can . Wait she turns around.
然后我们可以。 等她转身。
No, she doesn't. OK,
不，她没有。 好的，
that's just.
就是这样。
That's OK.
那没问题。
You can go.
你可以走了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
She got you, You
她得到了你，你
get the fuck out
滚出去
all right?
好的？
We're done with this place.
我们已经完成了这个地方。
Get the hell out of here now. Let's go
赶紧离开这里。 我们走吧
let's go to the next spot.
我们去下一个地方吧。
Next spot.
下一个地点。
you look for?
你在找什么？
You look cool as new.
你看起来像新的一样酷。
They the love school. Yeah.
他们爱学校。 是的。
Let's see a love school.
让我们看看爱情学校。
All right.
好的。
OK, now
好的，现在这是在这个区域找到蜡烛。
We were already here before, but she caught us last time.
我们之前已经在这里了，但她上次抓住了我们。
I think
我认为
yeah,
是的，
I still hear her
我仍然听到她
she has her little shrimps
她也让她的小虾们看着走廊。
she can come over here.
她可以过来。
Are you going to go back
你要回去还是要过来？
Oh, doesn't look like she has
哦，她好像没有
watch it everywhere.
到处看。
It's almost like she's trying.
这几乎就像她正在尝试一样。
I think she's trying to prevent us from, you know, bringing the candles out.
我认为她试图阻止我们，你知道，把蜡烛拿出来。
So fuck,
所以他妈的，
I really wish we had more incense.
我真希望我们有更多的香。
That's what lures them away, right?
这就是引诱他们离开的原因，对吧？
Ha ha ha ha.
哈哈哈哈。
Oh, no. Oh,
不好了。 哦，
oh, oh.
哦，哦。
She saw me oh.
她看见了我哦。
That's so lame.
那太蹩脚了。
How does she see me?
她怎么看我？
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
All right.
好的。
Yeah.
是的。
I got stabbed again.
我又被捅了一刀。
Oh, I'm dead.
哦，我死了。
I'm so dead. I'm so dad. It's not even funny
我死定了。 我太爸爸了 我死的程度甚至都不好笑。
Wait, wait,
等等，
wait. What?
等待。 什么？
I'm alive.
我还活着。
What?
什么？
alive?
活？
Oh, boy.
好家伙。
This is my birthday. Yes.
这是我的生日。 是的。
She was just teasing me.
她只是在逗我。
Well,
好，
I don't like being teased like that. It's
我不喜欢被这样取笑。 它是
ok. OK, ok, ok.
行。 好好好。
OK. OK.
好的。 好的。
You were slick. Were really slick.
你很圆滑。 真的很光滑。
We're slick right now.
我们现在很光滑。
Oh, there it is.
哦，是的。
Is that the. Candle?
是那个。 蜡烛？
Eh? No, that's not the candle.
诶？ 不，那不是蜡烛。
What's
什么是
where is the fucking candle then?
那该死的蜡烛在哪里？
Are you the candle?
你是蜡烛吗？
Oh, your incense
哦，你的香
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
How am I supposed to get to that? Is that it down there?
我该怎么做呢？ 是在下面吗？
Where's the incense, bro?
香在哪里，兄弟？
I don't know where the incense is at.
我不知道香在哪里。
that was the incense.
那是香。
Yeah, I'm trying to put it inside.
是的，我想把它放进去。
I don't have any to put any inside, though.
不过，我没有任何东西可以放在里面。
Well, maybe there's some in the bathroom.
嗯，也许浴室里有一些。
It's a ground.
这是一块地。
Yeah, there are some in the bathroom.
是的，浴室里有一些。
We got incense. OK, cool, cool, cool.
我们得到了香。 好吧，酷，酷，酷。
We can get them out the hallway now.
我们现在可以把他们从走廊里弄出来。
My God,
我的上帝，
thank fuck for that.
谢谢他妈的。
OK, let's get them out of the hallway.
好的，让我们把他们从走廊里弄出来。
He smells it
他闻到了
nice.
好的。
Oh, thank God.
哦，感谢上帝。
Oh, there's another.
哦，还有一个。
One right here.
一个就在这里。
I see. Help.
我懂了。 帮助。
So why are they so obsessed with it, though?
那么，为什么他们如此痴迷于它呢？
It's like a lure.
这就像一个诱饵。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
oh, oh.
哦，哦。
OK. Oh.
好的。 哦。
Nice.
好的。
Now we got to get the fuck out of here.
现在我们必须他妈的离开这里。
That's true. That's two candles down
那是真实的。 那是两根蜡烛
here. And
这里。 和
don't look in her.
不要看她。
Please don't walk in here.
请不要走进这里。
Please don't look in here plz don't look in here.Er.
请不要看这里请不要看这里。呃。
Oh. Oh, oh, oh,
哦。 哦哦哦，
dude.
老兄。
I think she came and saw the bathroom.
我想她是来看浴室的。
Otherwise, I would've heard all the breathing
否则，我会听到所有的呼吸声
so distracted by it.
如此分心。
Is it like drugs or something?
是像毒品还是什么？
Turn around.
回转。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I got the incense in there, so I think we're fine.
我把香放在里面了，所以我觉得我们很好。
Oh. Oh, oh, oh.
哦。 哦哦哦。
Oh, dear
哦，天哪，兄弟。
That's so fucking scary.
这太他妈可怕了。
Close.
关闭。
Yeah.
是的。
I try to do that
我试图这样做让她离开走廊，但是
she turned around.
她转身。
she is, oh.
她是，哦。
See those so close?
看到那些这么近了吗？
They are so close. Holy shit.
他们是如此接近。 天啊。
Why would she go.
她为什么要去。
Where am I. I am
我在哪里。我在
nowhere near you, that's for sure.
离你不远，这是肯定的。
No, close that door now.
不，现在关上那扇门。
some of you're gone
你们中的一些人走了
I think she's gone.
我想她已经走了。
Now I hear the box cutter.
现在我听到了切盒机的声音。
I don't want to leave the locker.
我不想离开储物柜。
Dude. I'm scared.
老兄。 我害怕。
I don't know if she's going to come in here or not.
我不知道她会不会来这里。
I think she's trying to trick me, like, oh.
我想她是想骗我，比如，哦。
No, it's totally OK, shoto.
不，完全没问题，shoto。
I'm not looking at you.
我不是在看你。
I'm not trying to look for you.
我不是要找你。
You can come out.
你可以出来。
The locker now.
现在的储物柜。
I'm not going to kill you.
我不会杀了你。
Shoto.
肖托。
Oh, she's not here, dude.
哦，她不在这里，伙计。
Do anything. I did it.
做任何事情。 我做到了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I think we did it. We did it.
我想我们做到了。 我们做到了。
We're looking at it.
我们正在研究它。
OK, let's get the hell out of here.
好吧，让我们离开这里。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Is this the last place that.
这是最后一个地方吗。
We have to go to?
我们要去吗？
I swear
我向上帝发誓，我以为我们以前在这里。
Are we not here already?
我们不是已经到了吗？
I think we're already here.
我想我们已经在这里了。
OK, and now we have one more candle
好的，现在我们又多了一根蜡烛，对吧？ 还有一个。
head in spirit.
精神上的头。
Was this
这是
all the way over that one before
一直超过之前的那个
I don't think.
我不这样认为。
Oh, I don't think we got the red threatening candles from this area yet.
哦，我认为我们还没有从这个地区得到红色的威胁蜡烛。
So let's look around
所以让我们环顾四周
oh. All right.
哦。 好的。
This should be the last one, right?
这应该是最后一个了吧？
Because there's only three,
因为只有三个，有没有
is there
只有三个
I don't know.
我不知道。
Or were there more.
或者还有更多。
Because there's it looks like there's more threats, Donna, missing.
因为看起来有更多的威胁，唐娜，失踪了。
I don't know where it's from.
我不知道它来自哪里。
Oh, here it wait on some down here.
哦，它在这里等着。
How do you get over here? Door
你怎么过来？ 门
elevator
电梯
let's take the elevator.
我们坐电梯吧。
The portable. Crox's without the r,
便携式的。  Crox's 没有 r，
so Cox?
所以考克斯？
the third floor.
三楼。
Yeah, that's where I'm going right now. No.
是的，这就是我现在要去的地方。 不。
Oh you know, it is the third floor right
哦，你知道吗，是三楼吧
all this doesn't look so good.
这一切看起来不太好。
Broadcasting room, broadcasting room.
广播室，广播室。
Let's go to a broadcasting room.
我们去广播室吧。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
There's, like, red threads.
有，像，红线。
What?
什么？
What? Huh?
什么？ 嗯？
Was that
那是
what?
什么？
They just can play noises.
他们只能播放噪音。
Like that and like that.
像那样那样。
Try to scare me.
试着吓唬我。
Dude, that's not cool.
伙计，这不酷。
I don't think
我不认为这是我们应该去的地方。
You know, the broadcasting room's lots.
你知道，广播室的地段。
I only we have the key for that are like
我只有我们有钥匙，就像访问一样。
Oh, no, we do.
哦，不，我们有。
We do have the key. What?
我们确实有钥匙。 什么？
I'm just dumb.
我只是愚蠢。
Attention, attention.
注意，注意。
Rumours spreading around the campus about a
校园里传出的谣言是
about a senior committing suicide.
关于一位老人自杀。
In the engineering building.
工程大楼内。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Please be aware that it was a hope.
请注意，这是一个希望。
Everyone please remain calm and do not spread further
请大家保持冷静，不要再散播谣言。
Thank you for your cooperation.
谢谢您的合作。
OK, I,
好的，我，
that's kind of cre...
那是一种创造...
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, my fucking God.
哦，我的他妈的上帝。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
So oh, no.
所以哦，不。
why why oh, fuck you.
为什么为什么哦，操你。
Game.
游戏。
I was just as I was really uncomfortable like nothing bad was going to happen.
我就像我真的很不舒服一样，好像没有什么不好的事情会发生。
It is.
这是。
Throw that shit in front of me.
把那玩意儿扔到我面前。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
OK, no,
好的，不，
this isn't a rumour.
这不是谣言。
Yeah, that's not a rumour.
是的，这不是谣言。
Literate just happened ok?
识字刚刚发生好吗？
I think that's what I should be.
我认为那是我应该的。
All of them, right?
所有的，对吧？
Oh, man,
天啊，
this game's unhealthy for my, for my heart.
这个游戏对我的，对我的心脏来说是不健康的。
Oh fuck with
哦，他妈的
what's down there.
下面是什么。
We been down there before.
我们以前去过那里。
You don't think you got any red threads down there, right?
你不认为那里有任何红线，对吧？
I think that's everything.
我认为这就是一切。
I believe, right?
我相信，对吧？
What about the fourth floor?
四楼呢？
Also, thank you for another drink.
另外，谢谢你再来一杯。
Guys, thank you so much for the hygiene
伙计们，非常感谢你们的卫生
I love you.
我爱你。
I love my guldies.
我爱我的古尔迪斯。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
No, I think on the fourth floor, it looks like
不，我想在四楼，它看起来像
there's a blood portal here
这里有一个血液传送门
I hate abandoned schools, man.
我讨厌废弃的学校，伙计。
The vibes are atrocious.
共鸣是残酷的。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
We've definitely already been here.
我们肯定已经来过这里了。
We don't need to be here anymore.
我们不再需要在这里了。
I know.
我知道。
Poke my head around just in case. Nope.
戳我的头以防万一。 没有。
Nothing
没有
yeah.
是的。
Let's go back down.
我们回去吧。
I think we finished
我想我们完成了
at least.
至少。
I'm pretty sure we did suck.
我很确定我们确实很糟糕。
You suck.
你好烂。
So let's go and see if the candles are good.
所以我们去看看蜡烛好不好。
Hello?
你好？
We done?
我们完成了？
Oh, it's open.
哦，它是开放的。
Oh. Oh, why?
哦。 哦为什么？
Oh, I don't like this.
哦，我不喜欢这样。
I don't like this one bit.
我不喜欢这一点。
Guys,
伙计们，
what is this?
这是什么？
I can't grab it.
我抢不走
Why not?
为什么不？
Let me grab it.
让我抓住它。
What's
什么是
what's this supposed to be?
这应该是什么？
It's like meets?
就像遇见？
good luck?
祝你好运？
What do you mean good luck?
祝你好运是什么意思？
It's locked.
它被锁定。
You have to get it opened.
你必须把它打开。
How? does use my hands
如何？ 确实用我的手
all these are a lot of things
所有这些都是很多东西
that it doesn't let me grab.
它不让我抓住。
For some reason.
由于某些原因。
A lot of them.
很多。
Oh, hey,
噢！嗨，
what's this?
这是什么？
Only water
只有水
above holy water. POG
圣水之上。  POG
oh. Where am I
哦。 我应该在哪里使用圣水，对吧？
On these things?
在这些事情上？
Why uh, do I make myself, like, a safe zone?
为什么，我要让自己成为一个安全区？
Uh, oh, ok.
嗯，哦，好的。
I get it.
我得到它。
Now I understand
现在我明白了
uh, why is it giving me
呃，为什么它给了我，就像这些很多，像，
spots you know, to try to make me feel safe?
你知道的地方，试图让我感到安全？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I feel like a boss if I is going to show up,
如果我要出现，我感觉自己像个老板，
you know,
你知道，
it's kind of like instincts
这有点像本能
and sticks at my my boss fight.
并坚持我的老板打架。
Instincts are coming kicking in.
本能正在发挥作用。
At the moment.
在这一刻。
No way.
没门。
What was that?
那是什么？
Now I need to deal.
现在我需要处理。
And once I get what I have to do, then
一旦我得到我必须做的事情，然后哦，嘿那里。
A hacksaw.
一把钢锯。
Right?
对？
So sorry, sorry, sorry,
很抱歉，对不起，对不起，
sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起。
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
both sorry.
都对不起。
Sorry,
对不起，
sorry, sorry.
实在抱歉。
Oh, yikes.
哦，哎呀。
OK. I think I understand
好的。 我想我明白为什么我现在必须这样做。
I think to use the hacksaw slowly to get out of here
我想用钢锯慢慢离开这里
and try to, like, avoid her
并尽量避开她
she doesn't know oh.
她不知道哦。
This dude.
这哥们
What?
什么？
What up?
怎么了？
Stop, stop.
停，停。
Oh, I don't like that music.
哦，我不喜欢那种音乐。
I don't like that music doing that.
我不喜欢那样做的音乐。
I'm so fucked.
我真他妈的。
I'm so fucked. I'm so fucked up.
我真他妈的。 我太他妈操蛋了。
Both my good.
都是我的好。
Hey, I'm here, I'm here. Disappear.
嘿，我在这里，我在这里。 消失。
Come over here and disappear.
过来这里消失。
OK? OK, ok.
好的？ 好的好的。
Now I have a chance to.
现在我有机会了。
Cut more
多切
those happening time.
那些发生的时间。
Pop oh.
流行哦。
Oh. This is bad.
哦。 这是不好的。
This is really bad.
这真的很糟糕。
Oh,
哦，
oh, fuck.
哦，操。
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
哦，操。 哦，操。 哦，操。
No, no, no.
不不不。
Stop it, stop it, stop it. I have holy water.
别了，别了，别了。 我有圣水。
I have the power of holy water on my side.
我身边有圣水之力。
You can't hurt me now.
你现在不能伤害我。
Wait,
等待，
wait.
等待。
Why is it not working?
为什么它不起作用？
Well, you want
嗯，你想要
it doesn't work anymore.
它不再起作用了。
What if it wasn't gonna work anymore?
如果它不再起作用怎么办？
Laughs My holy water I.
笑我的圣水。
She hear that.
她听到了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I think she does hear it.
我想她确实听到了。
Stop counting it.
别数了。
Go somewhere else. Leave me alone.
去别的地方。 请别打扰我。
Does she know where I am?
她知道我在哪里吗？
I think she does.
我想她会的。
Yeah, it was.
是的，是的。
Why was she?
为什么是她？
We should be moving like that.
我们应该这样移动。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
I'm safe here.
我在这里很安全。
We won't know.
我们不会知道的。
Not what?
不是什么？
I'm confused.
我很困惑。
What was that?
那是什么？
Oh, no.
不好了。
Get off of me. Get off of me!
你离我远点。 你离我远点！
Get off of me.
你离我远点。
Why? Why, why?
为什么？ 为什么为什么？
Why, why?
为什么为什么？
Why didn't you work that time?
那个时候你为什么不工作？
Oh, God, this is bad.
哦，上帝，这很糟糕。
Oh, sorry,
哦对不起，
sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起。
I'm not even halfway done.
我什至还没有完成一半。
Yeah,
是的，
that sucks, man.
太糟糕了，伙计。
You think it has?
你觉得有吗？
It's high.
它很高。
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
I doubt it does.
我怀疑它确实如此。
Let's just hurry up.
让我们快点。
Let's just hurry up and get some done.
让我们快点完成一些事情。
I'm I think she hears us
我是我认为她听到了我们的声音
oh, hold on.
哦，等一下。
I think you should lower down the the music, though, just a tad bit.
不过，我认为你应该把音乐调低一点。
So it's not like too obnoxious.
所以它不是太讨厌。
So we're going to be here for a bit.
所以我们要在这里待一会儿。
Yeah, ok.
是的，好的。
OK, ok. Punk pocket, pocket, pocket, pocket.
好的好的。 朋克口袋，口袋，口袋，口袋。
I've time now. I have time.
我现在有时间。 我有时间。
I have time, I have time.
我有时间，我有时间。
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck. No.
他妈的，他妈的，他妈的，他妈的，他妈的，他妈的。 不。
No, don't.
不，不要。
Oh. Why?
哦。 为什么？
How did she get me that time?
那个时候她是怎么弄到我的？
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
No way.
没门。
It's gonna make me redo it.
它会让我重做。
It's gonna make me fucking redo it. This game is cruel.
它会让我他妈的重做它。 这个游戏很残酷。
This game is.
这个游戏是。
So. Cruel. Why
所以。 残忍的。 为什么
oh, son of a bitch.
哦，狗娘养的。
Dude, this isn't.
伙计，这不是。
This is not going to be easy.
这并不容易。
All this is hard.
这一切都很难。
I'm going to learn to despise that chick.
我要学会鄙视那个小妞。
I all right.
我没事。
I just want to try again.
我只是想再试一次。
I listen.
我听。
I know, like, fully what to do now.
我完全知道现在该做什么。
It's just going to be difficult.
这将是困难的。
You know, it's going to be fucking difficult to
你知道，这将是他妈的很难
get away from her
离她远点
or trying to avoid her while we saw away at it.
或者在我们看到它的时候试图避开她。
It's just such a serious thing to sort through, though.
不过，这只是一件严肃的事情。
Do we even have this all?
我们甚至拥有这一切吗？
Well, was saw it
嗯，被看到了
all right.
好的。
There
那里
I believe this time, I think we can.
我相信这一次，我想我们可以。
We can do it now. We can do it this time.
我们现在可以做到。 这次我们可以做到。
Easy, easy peasy.
轻松，轻松。
Easy peasy.
十分简单。
Side by
并排
side now.
现在一边。
Sorry, sorry, sorry,
对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起。
Uh, I was.
呃，我是。
Opening.
开幕。
Oh, I see.
我懂了。
Hey, look at me.
嘿，看着我。
Look at me, look at me.
看着我，看着我。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
OK. Now I know where to
好的。 现在我知道把她困在哪里了。
Proper.
恰当的。
Proper
恰当的
sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry,
对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起，
sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起。
Sorry, sorry, sorry,
对不起，对不起，对不起，
Sorry.
对不起。
Fuck.
他妈的。
What the fuck? What the fuck? What the fuck?
什么鬼？ 什么鬼？ 什么鬼？
Go on oh.
继续哦。
Oh. Oh. Yes.
哦。 哦。 是的。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Hop the fuck.
跳他妈的。
Out of here.
离开这里。
I think we did it.
我想我们做到了。
I think what you need.
我想你需要什么。
To do it no.
不这样做。
Or holy.
或圣洁。
Water is holy water.
水是圣水。
Oh. Oh, oh, oh.
哦。 哦哦哦。
You're.
你是。
We did it.
我们做到了。
Let's go. OK.
我们走吧。 好的。
Oh, fuck.
哦，操。
Yeah. Hmm.
是的。 唔。
I told you.
我告诉你了。
Second try second try. Easy peasy.
第二次尝试第二次尝试。 十分简单。
Not even worried, bro.
也不担心，兄弟。
Not even worried.
甚至不担心。
God, I guess like luring her as far away from block.
天哪，我想就像引诱她远离街区一样。
Stop.
停止。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Bitch. No,
婊子。 不，
dude.
老兄。
All Oh, this is bad.
哦，这很糟糕。
This is really bad.
这真的很糟糕。
Well,
好，
oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Just oh.
只是哦。
This.
这。
Is that her?
是她吗？
Is I her lover?
我是她的情人吗？
I don't. Know.
我不。 知道。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
All better get out of here.
最好离开这里。
Yeah, yeah. Better get out of here, man.
是啊是啊。 最好离开这里，伙计。
Just you have to find her.
只是你必须找到她。
Yeah.
是的。
We're still looking for jane.
我们还在寻找简。
Godzilla, girl.
哥斯拉，女孩。
We're committed to finding our wife.
我们致力于寻找我们的妻子。
We we must really.
我们必须真的。
Love our wife. Wow.
爱我们的妻子。 哇。
OK. The ours.
好的。 我们的。
The only thing that could help me.
唯一能帮到我的。
The dagger given to me by the novice monk
新僧给我的匕首
some might have thought I was being gullible about this.
有些人可能认为我在这件事上很容易上当受骗。
I had to keep it away from him.
我不得不远离他。
Behind the cupboard would tell that someone help.
橱柜后面会告诉有人帮忙。
Then I do it all by myself,
然后我一个人做，
if not gone crazy.
如果没有发疯。
Forgot about Jane.
忘了简。
How can you forget about Jane?
你怎么能忘记简？
She's the entire.
她是整体。
Reason we're here.
我们在这里的原因。
I really don't think this was worth it, bruh.
我真的不认为这是值得的，布鲁。
Mika.
米卡。
Mika, your kind of go vigil for me. Go.
米卡，你为我守夜。 去。
Thank you so much for the read.
非常感谢您的阅读。
Me ga of your shameless good. All gone.
我嘎你不要脸的好。 全没了。
Assault, assault.
攻击，攻击。
I see you're
我看到你也试图在开关上更频繁地串起来。
Guys, if you don't know mika, she's also another
伙计们，如果你不认识米卡，她也是另一个
another friend of mine, so go check out her consensual.
我的另一个朋友，所以去看看她的同意。
She streams on both youtube and such, but I don't think as much on switch
她在 youtube 等上都流媒体，但我对 switch
just mostly youtube. So yeah, give her follow.
的看法并不多，主要是 youtube。 所以，是的，让她跟随。
Thank you for the ride and hope your stream was good.
感谢您的搭便车，并希望您的直播很好。
There we are. Just avoided.
我们在那里。 只是避而远之。
Lady with knife murdering us.
拿刀谋杀我们的女士。
By the way.
顺便一提。
I'm not a dog
我不是狗
as a woman.
作为一个女人。
Make that clear.
说清楚。
See, it's. It's not.
看，就是。 它不是。
It's not real. It's just.
这不是真的。 这只是。
It's just. Ha ha. Funny.
这只是。 哈哈。 有趣的。
Ha, dog.
哈，狗。
Ha you know it there for a second.
哈你知道它在那里一秒钟。
Um, I'm a regular boy
嗯，我是一个普通的男孩
named Paul.
名叫保罗。
Nice to meet you there on that's new here.
很高兴在那里见到你，这是新的。
I'll come.
我会来。
I'm playing a horror game today,
我今天在玩恐怖游戏，所以如果你不能忍受恐怖，那么我会说，
watch out.
小心。
Because it's pretty spooky.
因为它非常诡异。
So I'm paid for that. I put it on for free.
所以我为此付出了代价。 我免费戴上的。
Nobody paid for it.
没有人为此付出代价。
Why are you talking about I?
为什么说我？
Larry, put it on at the beginning of the screen. You can't.
拉里，把它放在屏幕的开头。 你不能。
You guys are gas lighters.
你们是打火机。
I got my shot.
我中枪了。
What is wrong? My shell.
怎么了？ 我的壳。
You guys are gas lighters.
你们是打火机。
What the heck?
有没有搞错？
Put it back. No,
放回去。 不，不，我不会。
I won't see that
我不会看到的
you're going to buy a gun.
你要买枪。
I gave it to you for free for 3 hours.
我免费给你3个小时。
OK, so awesome.
好的，太棒了。
Wait, where are we going, dude?
等等，我们要去哪里，伙计？
Where the fuck are we?
我们他妈在哪里？
It feels like
感觉就像我们一直在这座桥上经历了一个无限循环。
On this catwalk.
在这个T台上。
My crazy how
我的疯狂怎么
I only put on for 3 hours.
我只穿了3个小时。
That's your limit.
那是你的极限。
It's been 3 hours.
已经3个小时了。
If you want to walk again, then you're going to use your manifests.
如果您想再次走路，那么您将使用您的清单。
I don't know what to say.
我不知道要说什么。
My decision is final.
我的决定是最终的。
Licence, said Barak.
执照，巴拉克说。
Fuck you.
去你的。
Motherfucker.
混蛋。
There's a lot more red threads showing up, dude.
出现了更多的红线，伙计。
I don't know. OK, som someone bought it.
我不知道。 好的，有人买了。
OK, there you go.
好的，给你。
There you go.
你去吧。
I know who it was,
我知道那是谁，但我猜那是甘露果花得值。
I think
我认为
it's so goddamn quiet here.
这里真他妈的安静。
Am I am I even going the right way?
我是不是走对了路？
I mean, there's only one way to go.
我的意思是，只有一条路可以走。
There's so many red strings
有这么多红线
awesome behind me.
在我身后厉害。
Maybe this is intended.
也许这是故意的。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
The students spirit
学生精神
please cover up.
请掩盖。
That's so sassy of the daughter.
这女儿太嚣张了。
It is only more about its engine became major news
它只是更多关于它的引擎成为主要新闻
last time because of the death of one student.
上次是因为一名学生的死亡。
It must not be the same. The same. Thank you.
它一定不一样。 相同。 谢谢你。
Is this like
这就像我们看到的那位女士的一切吗
yeah. OK.
是的。 好的。
I just want to see if I was missing anything.
我只是想看看我是否遗漏了什么。
Is it quiet?
安静吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Why is it quiet then?
那为什么会安静呢？
Walking for a while. So
走了一会儿。 所以
what?
什么？
Who's happy over home
谁为回家或回家而高兴？
Hello?
你好？
Jane, you back here? It's toilet paper. Why?
简，你回来了？ 是卫生纸。 为什么？
Why do we have toilet paper on the on the table?
为什么我们的桌子上有卫生纸？
Is Tim like, you know, into
蒂姆喜欢，你知道，喜欢
exhibitionism?
暴露狂？
I'm just kidding.
我只是开玩笑。
I don't know. I'm trying to imply there.
我不知道。 我试图暗示那里。
I can't even bring this up.
我什至不能提出这个。
It's all tied down from the red thread. Tim.
这一切都是从红线系下来的。 蒂姆。
Oh, it's me again. Hey,
哦，又是我。 嘿，自从你老婆失踪后，你
you seem a bit strange.
你好像有点奇怪。
You don't act like yourself lately.
你最近不像你自己。
We're we're we're friends.
我们是我们是我们是朋友。
Aren't we? Mm hmm.
我们不是吗？ 嗯嗯。
If you need to talk to someone, I'm here. All right?
如果你需要找人谈谈，我在这里。 好的？
That's a good friend.
那是个好朋友。
Me back. I'm worried.
我回来。 我很担心。
That's a real good friend.
那是一个真正的好朋友。
Tim. Oh.
蒂姆。 哦。
It's me again. Depressed again. My bad.
又是我。 又郁闷了。 我的错。
Since your wife's disappearance, you
自从你妻子失踪后，你
you seem a bit strange.
你好像有点奇怪。
You don't act like yourself lately.
你最近不像你自己。
We're all.
我们都是。
What's with the knives? On the fridge? What's.
刀是怎么回事？ 在冰箱上？ 什么是。
If you need to talk to someone, I'm here.
如果你需要找人谈谈，我在这里。
All right.
好的。
Please call me back.
请给我回电。
I'm worried.
我很担心。
OK? I think we all go upstairs,
好的？ 我想我们都上楼了，好像下一个地方。
You don't have to see that.
你不必看到那个。
Like we're done with that.
就像我们完成了那样。
Those other spirits right Jane
那些其他的精神对简
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
The door's still there.
门还在。
Why am I worried?
我为什么担心？
Oh, my going so worried for
哦，我很担心
I think that's the only door
我认为这是我们唯一可以通过的门。
This is it.
就是这个。
Home? Yeah. Home, sweet home.
家？ 是的。 家，甜蜜的家。
All of this in our home.
这一切都在我们家。
Lowell,
洛厄尔，
hello.
你好。
Rozario, where's where's the wife?
罗萨里奥，妻子在哪里？
Uh. I'm
呃。 我实际上有点紧张。
It's not funny.
这不好笑。
I can't hear.
我听不见。
Why can't we open the door?
为什么我们不能开门？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Tomorrow.
明天。
Supposed to go
应该去
am I missing something?
我错过了什么吗？
The friend is.
朋友是。
Suss. What do you mean? The friend is lost.
苏斯。 你什么意思？ 朋友迷路了。
The friend is nice.
朋友很好。
He's genuinely cares about us.
他真的很关心我们。
And you're calling him Suss.
你叫他苏斯。
He's a good person.
他是个好人。
He's looking out for his friend.
他正在寻找他的朋友。
He cares about us.
他关心我们。
His word for us are computer's gone.
他对我们说的话是电脑没了。
What's.
什么是。
How am I supposed to play you legends now?
我现在应该怎么玩你的传奇？
Or Clarence
或克拉伦斯
if you overhear
如果你无意中听到
yours, call
你的，给这么多人打电话，苏西，最后你看起来像白痴
when you realise that they're good people.
当你意识到他们是好人时。
You call everything Suzie.
你把一切都称为苏西。
I swear,
我发誓，
I think you guys are Suzie.
我想你们是苏西。
You're projecting onto other characters
您正在投射到其他角色身上以转移您自己的 Suzie 动作
because you don't want to admit it.
因为你不想承认。
I feel like I'm missing something for real now, though.
不过，我觉得我现在真的错过了一些东西。
Like, where am I supposed to go?
比如，我应该去哪里？
Grab the ladder in the kitchen.
抓住厨房的梯子。
There's a ladder in the kitchen.
厨房里有梯子。
Where?
在哪里？
Oh, this is a small ladder.
哦，这是一个小梯子。
What's the what's the small ladder for?
小梯子是干什么用的？
Ha ha ha ha.
哈哈哈哈。
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈。
Nervous.
紧张的。
LAUGHTER Yeah.
笑声 是的。
The longer
越长
I am in this house, the more I want to get the fuck out again.
我在这房子里，我越想再他妈的出去。
It does not feel like home sweet home
感觉不像是温馨的家哦，哦，哦，哦。
Oh, Pug. OK,
哦，帕格。 好的，
just just say it.
就说吧。
Come in handy. What is it?
派上用场。 它是什么？
What was that? Huh?
那是什么？ 嗯？
Oh. Why
哦。 为什么
it's back there.
它回到了那里。
What's over here?
这里有什么？
I have a knife.
我有一把刀。
Why do I have a knife for it?
为什么我有一把刀呢？
What's back here?
什么回来了？
I don't know where to go.
我不知道该去哪里。
That.
那。
That was behind me.
那是在我身后。
Origin.
起源。
Jane, I'm Jane.
简，我是简。
I am Jane.
我是简。
What am I doing, though? Oh.
不过，我在做什么？ 哦。
Oh, man.
天啊。
Oh, oh. Oh, my God.
哦，哦。 我的天啊。
The fucking reflection in the mirror scared the shit out of me, man.
镜子里的倒影把我吓坏了，伙计。
Oh, I thought I was a.
哦，我以为我是一个。
Creature looking at me.
看着我的生物。
Uh, there's no place.
呃，没地方了。
Like home
像家
there's no place like home.
金窝银窝不如自己家里的狗窝。
You got a friend in me.
你在我里面有一个朋友。
Oh. Don't do that, bitch.
哦。 不要那样做，婊子。
Please stop
请停止
why are you knocking brooms over?
你为什么要把扫帚打翻？
Who? What are we looking for?
谁？ 我们在找什么？
Why are we trying to stab a monster?
为什么我们要刺伤怪物？
Resist spirit monster.
抵抗精神怪物。
Up. On the rooftop clap, clap, clap.
向上。 在屋顶上拍手，拍手，拍手。
Don't you
你不是吗
think.
思考。
Like there's the prayer again
就像祈祷又来了
I can open it.
我可以打开它。
I do.
我愿意。
I'm scared, man.
我很害怕，伙计。
I don't know. All this is so dark.
我不知道。 这一切都是那么的黑暗。
I need a flashlight.
我需要一个手电筒。
Is it making me go back
是不是让我回去
there's a new ghost.
有一个新的幽灵。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I can't believe there's going to be another new fucking ghost.
我不敢相信会有另一个新的他妈的鬼。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
Was this here before. Or.
以前在这里吗。 或者。
Yeah, it's a prayer.
是的，这是一个祈祷。
It's like some kind of mantra
就像某种咒语
oh, god.
天啊。
I don't want to look behind me.
我不想看我的身后。
No, I'm not looking behind me.
不，我没有在后面看。
Fuck you, ok?
去你妈的好吗？
Maybe I will. OK.
也许我会。 好的。
Nothing's ever
从来没有什么
funny. Come
有趣的。 来
laugh at me.
取笑我。
Was that
那是
really worried?
真的担心吗？
Really fucking worried?
真他妈担心？
Guys.
伙计们。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
Oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Is that OK?
那样可以么？
She I breathe like that because she's scared.
她我那样呼吸是因为她害怕。
The fuck are you
你他妈是
oh, stop. Why?
哦，停下来。 为什么？
You got to use me like that? Ma'am.
你非要这样利用我吗？ 女士。
Don't do that.
不要那样做。
Law it's
法律它是另一台收音机
oh. Man.
哦。 男人。
My hands are shaking like I actually can't control, like,
我的手在颤抖，就像我实际上无法控制一样，就像现在保持我的手稳定一样。
Is genuinely terrifying.
真的很可怕。
I didn't expect to be in this state again.
没想到又是这种状态。
After what we've been through in the game, but it pulls you straight back
在我们在游戏中经历过之后，但它会直接把你拉回来，直接。
Oh, that was hard.
哦，那很难。
Whoo!
哇！
Hello.
你好。
Are you a friend?
你是朋友吗？
Are you a friend? Friendly pal.
你是朋友吗？ 友好的朋友。
Buddy buddy buddy all buddy.
伙计，伙计，伙计们，伙计们。
All uh.
都呃。
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
You're not going to come alive or anything.
你不会活过来或任何事情。
Right and
对对对。
Right?
对？
Right,
对，
right.
对。
OK. I guess he's not
好的。 我猜他不是
and I'm very annoyed.
我很生气。
I'm so fucking paranoid here.
我在这里太他妈偏执了。
As I say.
正如我所说。
Oh, no, I think that's a walk inside huh?
哦，不，我认为那是走进去吧？
Oh, the singing stopped. Why?
哦，歌声停了。 为什么？
Oh, this is this fucking game.
哦，这该死的游戏。
Oh, God. Oh, no.
天啊。 不好了。
That's the same thing.
那是一样的。
From last time
从上次开始
I think I had to go back over here.
我想我必须回到这里。
Let's check
让我们检查
check and see.
检查并查看。
I missed out on anything.
我错过了任何事情。
You bitch, you bitch, bitch.
你个婊子，你个婊子，婊子。
No, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Let's not go that way.
我们不要那样做。
Yeah. Fuck that.
是的。 去他妈的。
Now I'm out of there.
现在我已经离开了。
I'm out of there.
我已经离开了。
Huh, huh, huh?
嗯嗯嗯？
We're going to.
我们准备去。
You know
你知道
what? What
什么？ 什么
Cool, cool.
酷，酷。
Very cool.
很酷。
Great moves.
大动作。
Keep it up.
保持。
Proud of you. I love this game.
为你骄傲。 我爱这游戏。
Jane.
简。
You got this.
你得到了这个。
Are you walking me out for ideal?
你是为了理想而带我出去吗？
Am I in a loop?
我在循环吗？
Why am I in a loop?
为什么我会陷入循环？
I remember this looks familiar.
我记得这看起来很熟悉。
You know what this.
你知道这是什么。
Reminds me of?
提醒我？
It reminds me of the ah, that one video
它让我想起了啊，那个视频
that was, like, give me a tour of your of his home.
就像，带我参观你的他家。
You guys know that really creepy youtube video?
你们知道那个真正令人毛骨悚然的 youtube 视频吗？
It like he's giving you a tour of his his house. Oh.
就好像他在带你参观他的房子一样。 哦。
My oh.
我的哦。
These are cool instruments.
这些都是很酷的乐器。
Which stones your reflection doing?
你的倒影在做什么石头？
They'll probably not
他们可能不会
what are we looking for?
我们在找什么？
And why do we have this knife?
为什么我们有这把刀？
Like, what are we trying to stab here?
就像，我们想在这里刺什么？
Obviously, she wants to stab something of the knife, and she has the knife out
很明显，她想用刀捅什么东西，她把刀拿出来了
of both corners.
的两个角落。
Nice was that coming from oh.
很好是来自哦。
Why it's very pretty.
为什么非常漂亮。
We all know
我们都知道
sounds pretty biting.
听起来很刺耳。
Is it coming from here?
是从这里来的吗？
Oh, I don't know where to go.
哦，我不知道该去哪里。
There's so many tight corridors, man.
有这么多狭窄的走廊，伙计。
It's making me feel a little claustrophobic.
这让我感到有点幽闭恐惧症。
Hey, where's Tim?
嘿，蒂姆在哪里？
Brazil. Jane, why are we in the situation?
巴西。 简，我们为什么会遇到这种情况？
The radio's gone. Oh, God, the radio is gone.
收音机不见了。 哦，天哪，收音机不见了。
Oh, God, that's bad.
哦，上帝，这很糟糕。
There.
那里。
Someone's there, someone's there, someone's there, someone's there,
有人在那里，有人在那里，有人在那里，有人在那里，有人在那里。
someone's there. Oh, God. Hey, help!
天啊。 嘿，救命！
Help! Help! Help!
帮助！ 帮助！ 帮助！
Get the basket.
拿到篮子。
Down. Help!
向下。 帮助！
Help! Someone!
帮助！ 有人！
Right, right.
是的是的。
Kylie, fuck off.
凯莉，滚蛋。
I have a knife.
我有一把刀。
I have a fucking knife.
我有一把他妈的刀。
I'm afraid to use it.
我害怕使用它。
You know,
你知道，普通99级，流氓哦，
oh, no.
不好了。
What?
什么？
What changed?
发生了什么变化？
What changed here, pop?
这里有什么变化，流行？
Give me out and get me out.
给我出去，让我出去。
I think that's a run.
我认为这是一个运行。
I think I have to run
我想我必须跑
fucking
他妈的
it's chasing me.
它在追我。
Leave
离开
me alone.
我一个人。
Stay with me.
留在我身边。
Why can't I move,
为什么我动不了
run, move oh.
跑，动哦。
TV continued on episode two
电视在第二集继续
to be continued on episode two.
将在第二集继续。
Don't I have episode two
我没有第二集吗
can I not continue
我不能继续吗
oh, I can't.
哦，我不能。
That's it.
这就对了。
All That's it.
仅此而已。
Wait,
等待，
it's. Huh?
它的。 嗯？
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
It's.
它的。
Do they have chapter. Two out right.
他们有章节吗。 两个出来的权利。
Now? Is in it out
现在？ 在里面
it's another game. Oh.
这是另一场比赛。 哦。
Oh, it's a whole nother game. OK.
哦，这完全是另一场比赛。 好的。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Yeah, I guess it's a whole.
是的，我想它是一个整体。
Different game then. Let me see.
那就另当别论了。 让我看看。
I check it on steam real fast.
我在steam上检查它真的很快。
Well, they can't say.
好吧，他们不能说。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Home sweet home.
家，甜蜜的家。
Ah, Episode two.
啊，第二集。
Yeah, there's in episode zero I hear. OK, I'll.
是的，我听说在第 0 集中。 好的，我会的。
Come out.
出来。
In 2019
2019年
hmm. OK, I see
唔。 好的我明白了
gotcha.
明白了。
All right. All right.
好的。 好的。
Yeah.
是的。
This is all there's, it's on this theme sorry now but.
这就是全部，现在是这个主题，抱歉。
Then that's enough.
那么这就足够了。
That was kind of an abrupt ending.
那是一个突然的结局。
Well we
那么我们
start oh.
开始哦。
Bro. What the fuck?
兄弟。 什么鬼？
We did it, though.
不过，我们做到了。
I think we finished
我想我们完成了
yeah, that's it for.
是的，就是这样。
That's it for the first game.
第一场比赛就是这样。
This was really cool.
这真的很酷。
I enjoyed this a lot.
我非常喜欢这个。
I honestly really enjoyed this a lot.
老实说，我真的很喜欢这个。
It was really fun to play.
玩起来真的很有趣。
Like,
像，
Thank you guys so much for the recommendation.
非常感谢你们的推荐。
Otherwise, I wouldn't have known about this game.
否则，我不会知道这个游戏。
Yeah.
是的。
Like I said before, the fact that there's so much like, what's it
就像我之前说的，事​​实如此之多，它是什么
culture ingrained into the video game
电子游戏中根深蒂固的文化非常酷，对吧？
And it's really interesting to learn about while you're still getting spooked
当你还在被吓到的时候去了解它真的很有趣
from all the horror elements of a, of a typical survival horror.
来自一个典型的生存恐怖的所有恐怖元素。
Like the law is good and the stories are nice to know
就像法律很好，故事很高兴知道
it took me until now to figure out, oh, like all these monsters that we've been
直到现在我才弄清楚，哦，就像我们看到的所有这些怪物一样，就像那些来自简的梦之类的东西，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
Hmm. But I think this is a good place to start for today.
唔。 但我认为这是今天开始的好地方。
Yes. Since we've already played through two games we can just go back to the.
是的。 由于我们已经玩了两场比赛，我们可以回到过去。
Yeah, let's go back.
是的，我们回去吧。
To the bedroom and talk for a little bit before we hand it off. OK,
在我们交出它之前，到卧室和谈一谈。 好的，
mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Because I think if I want to play episode two,
因为我想如果我想玩第二集，
I'll save it for another week.
我会再保存一个星期。
Yeah, I'd probably save the game for next week or something
是的，我可能会把比赛留到下周或类似的时间，但下周会有很多召唤。
I don't know if we can.
我不知道我们是否可以。
We have time for it next week, but I'll keep you guys updated on that.
我们下周有时间，但我会及时通知你们。
All right.
好的。
Give me a second and then switch over.
给我一秒钟，然后切换。
Where is the bedroom
卧室在哪里
hold on
坚持，稍等
me one moments
我一瞬间
OK? Oh,
好的？ 哦，
and for some reason, the my chat is gone.
由于某种原因，我的聊天不见了。
It disappeared on me.
它在我身上消失了。
I oh, come back
我哦，回来
guys. Come back.
伙计们。 回来。
Why? Just disappear.
为什么？ 就这样消失。
Fuck, OK.
妈的，好吧。
Oh, well, that's fine.
哦，那很好。
Give me a second. I'm good.
你稍等一会儿。 我很好。
Turn some music while we are chillin shot first for a bit. OK,
在我们先冷静一下的时候打开一些音乐。 好的，
so we're gonna be ending this off in a bit.
所以我们将很快结束这一切。
OK? For people
好的？ 对于还在这里的人，我确实想谈谈下周会发生什么。
Ah, I don't know exactly
啊，具体不知道
what we're going to be doing for.
我们将要做什么。
Me. For this coming week, but I know there's going to be a lot of clubs so
我。 在接下来的一周，但我知道会有很多俱乐部，所以
I think we're planning to have a.
我想我们正计划有一个。
Nice round.
好圆。
We're playing
我们在玩
a a club of Vox again and Ike and Remo
又是一个 Vox 俱乐部，还有 Ike 和 Remo
on a Tuesday,
在一个星期二，我们将要玩一个叫做迷宫的游戏。
And if you guys ever heard of it, but I heard phenomenal.
如果你们听说过它，但我听到了惊人的。
Luca Boogie really enjoyed the game, I should say.
Luca Boogie 真的很喜欢这场比赛，我应该说。
And so I want to give the game a try and see what it's about.
所以我想试试这个游戏，看看它是关于什么的。
Phenomenon told me it was really fucking fun
现象告诉我这真的很他妈的有趣，她真的很害怕，她是啊，
she's also another like, you know, kind of like a horror film.
她也是另一个，你知道的，有点像恐怖片。
So because she's like, she's like a big family nerd.
所以因为她喜欢，所以她就像一个大家庭书呆子。
And she said that this one was really fun.
她说这个真的很好玩。
So I think we're going to be playing that with Vox.
所以我认为我们将与 Vox 一起玩。
I can review on Tuesday and then on Wednesday
我可以在星期二复习，然后在星期三复习
we're going to have a violent collab.
我们将进行一场激烈的合作。
With Shu.
与舒。
Lily Picchu and Box Box.
百合比丘和盒子。
I think Shu should be back by Wednesday.
我想舒应该在星期三之前回来。
And then I think Uki said that
然后我想 Uki 说他想玩一个叫做，嗯，
Operation Tango with me next week,
下周和我一起进行探戈行动，但我们还没有决定日期，所以也快到了。
So yeah, I'll collab of Uki and we have a gala with Shu, Lily and Box Box.
所以，是的，我将与 Uki 合作，我们将与 Shu、Lily 和 Box Box 举办一场盛会。
And then on Tuesday we're going to be playing something with the
然后在星期二我们将与
what's it with
它是什么
Voxer I can reveal.
Voxer 我可以透露。
And also, ah,
而且，啊，它现在有点悬而未决。
But
但
me and sekouno have talked about a potential collab.
我和 sekouno 谈到了潜在的合作。
I don't know if it's going to be this week or like next week,
不知道是这周还是下周，
I mean or the upcoming week, but we want to play something
我的意思是或即将到来的一周，但我们想和对方一起玩一些东西，并且其他一些人是朋友。
It might just be Valorant and to be honest,
这可能只是勇敢的，老实说，
I think we're just going to do Valorant and or something, but I'll,
我想我们会做一些勇敢的事情，但我会，
I'll let you know
我会让你知道
as soon if we figure things out because this wants to make people aware.
只要我们弄清楚事情，因为这想让人们意识到。
That.
那。
Oh, come
哦，来吧
I play coma. what's coma.
我玩昏迷。 什么是昏迷。
Coma friend.
昏迷的朋友。
I've never heard of that.
我从来没有听说过。
I never heard that game before.
我以前从未听说过那场比赛。
What the heck is coma ?
昏迷是什么鬼？
what.
什么。
Yeah, I think if I play with fire psych or not, I think I'm going to think
是的，我想无论我是否玩火心理，我想我会认为我们会在
we're going to do something off Luka to Luka and Pichu.
Luka 和 Luka 和 Pichu 之间做一些事情。
And also.
并且。
I think it's probably.
我想大概是这样。
Just going to be more violence, to be honest,
老实说，只会变得更加暴力，除非我们想出一个不同的恐怖合作游戏。
But yeah, so there's a lot there is.
但是，是的，所以有很多。
A lot coming up and I am really excited
很多事情即将到来，我真的很高兴能够玩更多的朋友游戏。
And friends and.
和朋友和。
You know, more excuses, fine workings of friends.
你知道，更多的借口，朋友的好工作。
It always makes me happy. So yeah.
它总是让我开心。 是的。
You got troubles there's no gear.
你有麻烦没有装备。
That like there's no guarantee.
就像没有保证一样。
Like, what's it that
比如，那是什么
the collab with uki is going to be this coming week though
与 uki 的合作将在下周进行
that's not soccer since he's still on vacation.
那不是足球，因为他还在度假。
He'll probably be back around once day, so probably be on the weekend.
他可能会每天回来一次，所以可能是在周末。
I think
我认为
OK. Oh.
好的。 哦。
But that's just.
但这只是。
To give everybody idea about what's coming up.
让每个人都知道即将发生的事情。
So if you guys are excited as much as I am, I'm going to read through
所以如果你们和我一样兴奋，我现在要通读所有的捐赠和东西。
Again, I don't know, I might shop boxes in showing up.
再说一次，我不知道，我可能会在店里出现。
It's like.
它像是。
It's me.
是我。
Oh, there it is.
哦，是的。
you guys are back. POG.
你们回来了。  POG。
He did it.
他做到了。
I did do it. We beat the game.
我确实做到了。 我们击败了比赛。
Thank you for the $10. Oh, no, Yuki.
谢谢你的 10 美元。 哦，不，由纪。
Lucky thing for that.
幸运的事情。
2000 bits Sammy Thank you for the sub.
2000 位 Sammy 谢谢你的订阅。
Maybe. Thank you for the dona as well.
也许。 也谢谢你的捐赠。
Pluto thank you for the 30 months, welcome back
冥王星感谢你的30个月，欢迎回来
I see cool guy.
我看到帅哥
Thank you for the three months.
谢谢你的三个月。
There's a lot of results earlier.
前面有很多结果。
Thank you so much for the results guys.
非常感谢你们的结果。
And Zal Rachel thank you for the 1000 bits.
Zal Rachel 感谢您提供的 1000 位。
Zoe thank you for the dona.
佐伊谢谢你的捐赠。
I think you're going to have
我想你会很难看我和那位女士玩
yeah.
是的。
The fucking.
他妈的。
That. Spirit is really creepy.
那。 精神真的很可怕。
She is so fucking creepy, man.
她真是太他妈毛骨悚然了，伙计。
But I mean, we made it through is difficult, but we made it through also.
但我的意思是，我们挺过来了很困难，但我们也挺过来了。
Lucky man.
幸运儿。
Thank you for the tier three sub.
谢谢你的第三层潜艇。
Welcome to the channel
欢迎来到频道
guys.
伙计们。
You want to know something?
你想知道些什么吗？
We have like 12,000
我们有大约 12,000
like subscribers to the channel.
喜欢频道的订阅者。
Like that's a lot.
像这样的很多。
That's a lot of, that's a lot of guildies.
那是很多，那是很多guildies。
I think there's so many of you and like,
我想你们有很多人喜欢，
I mean we already have a lot of followers, but like in terms of like,
我是说我们已经有很多追随者了
YouTube membership, it's like Twitch subscriptions.
YouTube 会员资格，就像 Twitch 订阅一样。
OK, thank you so much for the, you know,
好的，非常感谢你，你知道，
you so much for subscribing and like giving
你非常喜欢订阅，喜欢赠送这么多礼物订阅，并将更多的人带入我们的家庭。
It means a lot guys.
这意味着很多人。
it's growing every day and it makes me happy,
它每天都在增长，它让我快乐，
like whenever I'm on somebody else's like channel on twitch
就像每当我在 twitch
or just like , it doesn't make me like, you know, a bit.
上的其他人喜欢的频道上一样，或者只是喜欢，它不会让我喜欢，你知道，有点。
I'll just like giddy inside when I see somebody using an email,
当我看到有人使用电子邮件时，我会感到头晕目眩，
I'm like, all there solve.
我喜欢，一切都解决了。
Hey there, I see you.
你好，我看见你了。
There is.
有。
All. Milk. Thank you for all the bits.
全部。 牛奶。 谢谢你的一切。
And Michael, thank you for all the bits too.
迈克尔，也感谢您提供的所有信息。
There's a lot of bits. Holy shit.
有很多位。 天啊。
So many bits and anything you for all the bits as well are shoddy.
这么多的比特和你所有的比特都是伪劣的。
Thank you for the on, on your bits and so good.
谢谢你，你的位，太好了。
Thank you for that.
谢谢你。
I know absolutely adore your shoes, especially when you play horror games.
我知道绝对喜欢你的鞋子，尤其是当你玩恐怖游戏的时候。
A lot of pressure recently crying face if possible.
最近压力很大的哭脸如果可以的话。
Can you say a few words of encouragement for me and friends in the same situation.
能不能对我和同样情况的朋友说几句鼓励的话。
As me could ever.
就像我一样。
Hey, if
嘿，如果你压力很大，记得休息一下，好吗？
It's totally fine to just sit back and take it like it's.
坐下来接受它是完全没问题的。
Equally. As good.
相等。 一样好。
It's like do your work, but it's also good.
这就像做你的工作，但它也很好。
So like, you know, balance it out and treat yourself right.
所以，你知道，平衡它并正确对待自己。
So hey, don't overdo it.
所以，嘿，不要过度。
Otherwise yeah, you're going to over burn yourself out and
否则，是的，你会过度燃烧自己
that's not good.
这是不好的。
But hey, I don't know what you're doing.
但是，嘿，我不知道你在做什么。
I don't know what some of you guys are doing. But good luck, OK?
我不知道你们中的一些人在做什么。 但祝你好运，好吗？
You got this
你得到了这个
I believe in you,dude .
我相信你，伙计。
I see. What was I saying?
我懂了。 我刚才说了什么？
If you're taking recommendations, I think horsing around might be to your liking.
如果您正在接受建议，我认为四处游荡可能符合您的喜好。
What is haunting ground haunting ground game.
什么是鬼屋鬼屋游戏。
All this is a PlayStation.
这一切都是 PlayStation。
Two game. I don't think I can play this coming up.
两场比赛。 我不认为我可以玩这个即将到来。
Why so excited for the following streams and collab.
为什么对以下流和合作如此兴奋。
Yeah, that's that's a really
是的，那是真的
that's a PlayStation two.
那是PlayStation 2。
Yeah, I don't think I can play that is I don't really have a PlayStation two
是的，我不认为我可以玩，除非我可以在我的
unless I can play it on my PlayStation four.
PlayStation 4 上玩，否则我并没有真正的 PlayStation 2。
I'm not sure
我不确定
are all a second year for the time until the end.
都是第二年的时间，直到结束。
It makes me feel sad. All your talk about little nightmares.
这让我感到难过。 你所有关于小噩梦的谈话。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Yeah, it was a really sombre ending.
是的，这是一个非常阴暗的结局。
I talking it thinking about it, how things are.
我谈论它思考它，事情是怎样的。
I guess six.
我猜是六个。
Did like maybe she realised like who he actually was
确实喜欢也许她意识到他实际上是谁
and like, you know, dropped him to like prevent
就像，你知道的，放弃他喜欢阻止
to just keep the loop going to save herself or
只是保持循环来拯救自己或
I don't know, it's hard to think.
我不知道，很难想象。
I don't know why, why that happened.
我不知道为什么，为什么会这样。
And why she did that friend.
以及为什么她会做那个朋友。
Because I'm Yeah.
因为我是啊。
Like is I'm not, I don't understand it completely as to the reasoning
就像我不是，我不完全理解它的推理
why she needed to let go of mono and let him die
为什么她需要放手让他死，但是啊，现在我看着他就像你知道的那样变成了帽子男。
We stick together uh.
我们团结在一起，嗯。
I see what else yuki thank you for another 2000 bits.
我看到 yuki 还感谢您提供了另外 2000 位。
So thank you so much. Yuki
所以非常感谢你。 由纪
Yay. You all right?
耶。 你没事吧？
I think that's it.
我想就是这样。
They have read everything.
他们已经阅读了所有内容。
They could be a little bit small.
它们可能有点小。
Okey dokey.
对。
Bros Siren and Fatal Frame are also really good.
Bros Siren 和 Fatal Frame 也很不错。
I've heard a lot of good. Things about Fatal Frame.
我听过很多好话。 关于致命框架的事情。
我爱你，我爱你
我爱你我爱你
Yeah.
是的。
I feel for Ms.
我对小姐姐有好感
The for the cameras. Right.
用于相机。 对。
But I've heard.
但我听说过。
I've heard good things about Fatal Frame.
我听说过关于致命框架的好消息。
Oh, know, you guys like Fatal Frame? Up.
哦，知道吗，你们喜欢 Fatal Frame 吗？ 向上。
Someone said White day was another good one.
有人说白色情人节是另一个好日子。
Why? It's a horror game.
为什么？ 这是一个恐怖游戏。
You can see side destiny.
你可以看到侧面的命运。
And notorious cult classic Korean horror.
还有臭名昭著的邪教经典韩国恐怖片。
Sneak in to school at midnight here.
半夜在这里偷偷上学。
It's from your sweetheart's diary
它来自你爱人的日记，并陷入了一场可怕的猫捉老鼠游戏。 唔。
hold on .
坚持，稍等 。
It looks like it's.
看起来就是这样。
In me.
在我。
Well received I'm not sure
好评 我不确定
I'll look at it, though.
不过，我会看看它。
We'll get a little bit more.
我们会得到更多。
OK, we're going to end the stream off
好的，不过，我们要在这里结束直播，今晚我要去找人看书。 好的，
thank you for coming by, guys.
谢谢你们的光临，伙计们。
And I'll see you tomorrow because I remember you playing some.
我明天见，因为我记得你玩过一些。
Alien isolation.
外星人隔离。
Tomorrow. I'll be excited for that
明天。 我会为此感到兴奋。
I love Alien. I love aliens so much.
我爱外星人。 我非常喜欢外星人。
Now we'll get to go live again tomorrow at 9 a.m.
现在我们将在明天早上 9 点再次上线。
and then we're going to have our YouTube stream on Sunday.
然后我们将在周日进行 YouTube 直播。
So, yeah, for people that don't know, there's going to be a impromptu
所以，是的，对于不知道的人，会有一个即兴的
YouTube stream on a Sunday, we're going to be doing a Q&A.
YouTube 周日直播，我们将进行问答。
So use the hashtag, #AskShoto or if you have any questions.
因此，请使用主题标签 #AskShoto 或如果您有任何问题。
OK, I'm going to be scrolling through all of it.
好的，我将滚动浏览所有内容。
So finally, we do it right here.
所以最后，我们在这里做。
Ask Shoto.
问肖斗。
on Twitter.
在推特上。
Use this, use this.
用这个，用这个。
All right.
好的。
And then I'll go through it and answer anything you guys want
然后我会通过它并回答你们想要的任何东西
or I'll try to answer most questions for the US on this stream, OK?
或者我会尝试在这个直播中回答美国的大部分问题，好吗？
As we've never really had an official
因为我们从来没有真正的官员
Q&A dedicated stream, I think that'll be kind of fun, right?
Q&A 专用流，我认为这会很有趣，对吧？
While I get used to how YouTube works,
虽然我习惯了 YouTube 的工作方式，
all right, guys,
好吧，伙计们，
go play an ad break and then I'll look for somebody to read.
去打个广告，然后我会找人看。
So give me a second.
所以给我一秒钟。
Be right back
马上回来
let's see who's alive right now.
让我们看看现在谁还活着。
Play the ad. You
播放广告。 你
lit up with the.
点亮了。
Bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum
呸呸呸呸呸呸呸呸呸呸呸
bum bum bum
呸呸呸
you've got a friend and me.
你有一个朋友。
You got a friend . who is alive.
你有一个朋友。 谁还在线。
Who's live right now.
现在谁在直播。
I think we can
我想我们可以去给我们的爱
wait.
等待。
No one's live right now.
现在没有人直播。
Right now. Huh?
现在。 嗯？
OK, maybe I go through the arm.
好吧。
Maybe I can go through the Vtuber Tag.
也许我可以通过 Vtuber 标签。
And look for somebody new tonight. Probably.
寻找今晚的新人。 大概。
That sounds like kinda fun idea.
这听起来是个有趣的主意。
There's momo.
我看看，有沫沫。
Who else is around?
还有谁在附近？
But let me see if I could find somebody new too right.
但是让我看看我是否能找到一个合适的新人。
Right there.
在那里。
Is there anything I wouldn't do for you?
有什么我不会为你做的吗？
There is.
有。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
There's a lot of people in the Vtuber tag at the moment that we can probably try
目前Vtuber标签中有很多人，我们可能可以尝试看看他们。 唔。
they have really cute model.
他们有非常可爱的模组。
Smarter than I am. And
比我好看和哈。
you know what? Sure.
你知道吗？ 当然。
However, I won't. Meet new people.
但是，我不会。 认识新的人。
I will meet new people as a. Result, from
我会结识新朋友。 结果。
All right.
好的。
In we go.
我们进去。
As the years go by.
随着时间的流逝。
Thank you guys for coming by tonight.
谢谢大家今晚光临。
And I'll see it tomorrow.
我明天会看到它。
All right.
好的。
For being a company throughout these horror games, it means a lot.
作为一家制作这些恐怖游戏的公司，这意味着很多。
I've had a lot of fun getting to play
我可以通过再次玩小噩梦，也可以玩甜蜜的家来获得乐趣。
Please, if you know any more games,
如果你知道更多的游戏，请
if you guys know any.
如果你们知道的话。
More games are like home sweet home, which are like, you know, have
更多的就像家一样甜蜜的家，就像，你知道的，有
have like what's it?
有什么喜欢的吗？
culture inside into the horror like that, which is really cool.
那样的恐怖里面掺杂文化的元素，这真的很酷。
and is also like that like I guess that's a good like
也是这样，我想这是一个很好的爱好。
description of a game that I like to try and play is like games
我喜欢尝试和玩的游戏的描述就像甜蜜之家
like Home Sweet Home , Outlast, Alien Isolation.
Home、Outlast、Alien Isolation 之类的游戏。
Resident Evil Seven Well, less. On the.
生化危机七？好吧，
Action aspects, you know, and more on like the survival aspect of horror
动作方面，你知道，还有更多像恐怖的生存方面，试图像你知道的那样，让我们​​的方式像隐形一样
through enemies and like do puzzles and shit like that.
一路割草，解开谜题和那样的玩法。
Please make recommendations.
请提出建议给我好吧。
Oh, fearless puppy.
哦，无畏的小狗。
Thank you for the $10.
谢谢你的 10 美元。
Can I have lots of kisses?
我可以有很多吻吗？
Mwah.
哇。
Goodnight.
晚安。
take care bye.
保重，再见。
Bye. Bye.
再见。 再见。
See you next time.
下次见。
(singing)
（唱歌）
You got a friend in me.
你在我这有一个朋友。